[{"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Classes are small, so students and faculty can build close relationships, delve into research and explore across academic fields. More than half of all Pomona students work closely with professors in research projects, receiving academic and financial support for a deeper approach to learning."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "WATCH: Faculty and Student Research"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "More than 90% of our students live on campus here in Southern California all four years, and many professors live within five miles of campus. New collaborations or discussions can spring up anywhere \u2013 a residence hall, club meeting or at lunch with a professor."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Partnering with ResearchersHow does YouTube partner with researchers?"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Brand resourcesAccess brand resources such as our YouTube logo, color palettes, and permissions form"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "We also recognize that the best way to quickly remove content is to anticipate problems before they emerge. Our Intelligence Desk monitors the news, social media, and user reports to detect new trends surrounding inappropriate content, and works to make sure our teams are prepared to address them before they can become a larger issue."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty Employment Opportunities"}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College was established in 1887 on a campus designed to recreate the best of the eastern Ivy League universities, while at the same time offering the beautiful Southern California lifestyle. Located in Claremont, CA, Pomona has approximately 1,500 undergraduate students and a student to faculty ratio of 8 to 1."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "We are continually ranked among the best colleges in the nation on Kiplinger's Personal Finance, The Princeton Review, and the Fiske Guide to Colleges. We inspire our students to take risks and we support them in their mission to make a real difference in the world."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "We seek to engage and reward our employees who are professionals of the highest caliber and quality, who value our College\u2019s intimate community and historic roots, and who contribute to the ethics, talents and excellence of our administration and faculty in a collaborative environment of equal opportunity, intellectual development, personal growth, and liberal arts education that leads the nation and the world."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "EmploymentStaff Employment OpportunitiesStaff Employment Opportunities for Current EmployeesFaculty Employment OpportunitiesPomona Students Employment Opportunities"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty Employment Opportunities"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Find the faculty, staff, and offices you need to get in touch with."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Please indicate a contact person for your event, so that interested participants can efficiently learn more about your event."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Descriptions are required for all event submissions. Please refer to thePomona College Style Guidewhen creating your description."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College is widely regarded as one of the world\u2019s leading liberal arts colleges, offering an ideal environment for intellectually curious students to pursue their academic and life goals."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Throughout its history, Pomona College has educated students of exceptional promise. We gather individuals, regardless of financial circumstances, into a small residential community that is strongly rooted in Southern California yet global in its orientation."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Through close ties among a diverse group of faculty, staff and classmates, Pomona students are inspired to engage in the probing inquiry and creative learning that enable them to identify and address their intellectual passions. This experience will continue to guide their contributions as the next generation of leaders, scholars, artists and engaged members of society to fulfill the vision of the College\u2019s founders: to bear their added riches in trust for all."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The best evidence of the soundness of Pomona\u2019s educational philosophy is the success of its graduates. Pomona alumni are leaders in a variety of fields \u2013 from medicine, public policy, and the arts to scientific research, journalism, business and the law."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "visitclaremont2,319Tag #shareclaremont \u2014 share hotel stays, craft beers & spirits, dining, boutiques, galleries & more. Claremont is LA's College & Arts town!visitclaremontViewOct 11OpenLooking for the perfect weekend getaway? Head to Claremont, CA! \ud83c\udf89 Bring your friends, family, and even your pups for an unforgettable adventure. Start by exploring the historic Claremont Packing House with its cool shops and restaurants. Play retro games at Lost Levels and catch a film at Laemmle\u2019s Claremont! \ud83c\udfae\ud83c\udf7fPick up goodies from The Cheese Cave and enjoy a picnic at the serene California Botanic Garden. Don`t miss the Claremont Lewis Museum of Art in the charming Claremont Depot. For meals, enjoy lunch al fresco at the Claremont Village Square and indulge in incredible dinners at Bardot or Union on Yale. \ud83c\udf7d\ufe0fOn Sunday, shop local at the Farmers & Artisans Market. With free parking and the option to take the Metrolink straight to the village, getting around is a breeze. So, what are you waiting for? Book your fun-filled weekend in Claremont now! \ud83d\udecd\ufe0f\ud83c\udf3f\u2728#claremontca  #weekendgetaway  #travelwithfriends #dogfriendlytravel #exploreclaremont #shareclaremont #visitclaremont #socaladventures Best Things TO Do in Claremont, CA -  Weekend Getaway to Claremont - Where to eat and what to do in Claremont, California@uniononyale @bardotclaremont @lostlevelsclaremont @claremontpackinghouse @claremontfarmersmarket @californiabotanicgarden @claremontcheese @laemmleclaremont...392visitclaremontViewOct 7OpenFall in love with Claremont on a beautiful autumn day, where the crisp air and vibrant foliage set the perfect stage for romance and adventure. \ud83c\udf42\u2764\ufe0f Hop on a bike and ride through the picturesque campuses of the Claremont Colleges, where tree-lined paths and stunning architecture create a postcard-worthy backdrop. Or take a Lyft to the Webb Schools campus to check out fossils at the Alf Museum.For a truly magical moment, catch the sunrise at James Turrells`s Skyspace, \"Dividing The LIght\", where the early morning light dances through his architectural masterpiece, filling the space with ethereal colors. As the day unfolds, head to Ironbark Ciderworks for a refreshing cider\u2014perfectly crafted from local ingredients and brimming with fall flavors.Spend the afternoon shopping in Claremont Village, where you\u2019ll find everything from unique boutiques to cozy bookstores. As evening approaches, dine at one of Claremont\u2019s cutest cafes, where delicious food and a charming atmosphere make for a perfect meal.End your day by watching the sunset in the nearby mountains, where the sky turns shades of orange and pink, casting a warm glow over the landscape. Whether you\u2019re here for a romantic getaway or to soak in the season`s beauty, Claremont offers a day full of moments to fall in love with. \ud83c\udf05\ud83d\udeb4\u200d\u2642\ufe0f\ud83c\udf41#claremontca #claremontcalifornia #visitclaremont #discoverclaremontThings to do in Claremont * Claremont in the fall * Claremont in Autumn...571visitclaremontViewOct 6Open\ud83c\udf83\ud83d\udc7b Spooky season is in full swing in Claremont, and the Halloween vibes are stronger than ever! From spine-chilling thrills to festive fun, October in Claremont brings all the spooky magic we love.Past years have been filled with memorable moments (let`s take a quick look)! We loved celebrating D\u00eda de los Muertos at Rio de Ojas, getting into the Halloween spirit with Aromatique Skin and Body Care and finding mystical treasures at Buddhamouse Emporium. \ud83d\udd6f\ufe0f\u2728We never forget to stop by SMELL in the Claremont Packing House for all things sweet and eerie, and hopefully it is happening again this year, but if you get a chance, explore the haunted beauty of the California Botanic Garden\u2019s Bootanical Family Night Walk! Check their calendar for other fun happenings, as they are constantly creating new events.\ud83c\udf3f\ud83c\udf83 And of course, no October is complete without the Village Venture, where costumes, crafts, and chills come together for a thrilling good time. \ud83d\udc7b\ud83c\udf42Happening October 26th all day!Things to do in Claremont * Claremont experiences * Family friendly Claremont * Claremont in October * Halloween * Village Venture * Family Fun#HalloweenInClaremont #ClaremontSpookySeason #VillageVenture #DiaDeLosMuertos #BootanicalNight #OctoberVibes...260visitclaremontViewOct 3OpenWe\u2019re so excited about the Village Venture, happening October 26th in Claremont. \ud83c\udf83There will be over 450 vendors and music, food, fun events!Reposting here with a great video showing you all the fun!Save this post so you don\u2019t miss it\u2026 coming soon! Will you come by and say hi?Claremont Village Venture \u2022 things to do in Claremont, California \u2022 weekend events \u2022 October events #villageventure #shareclaremont...692visitclaremontViewSep 30OpenTop FREE Things to do in Claremont, California \u2b50\ufe0fSAVE this post for your next visit!It\u2019s true, the best things in life are free! There is no shortage of free things to do in the beautiful, tree-filled, hidden gem of Claremont.Here are ten ways to enjoy your visit, TOTALLY FREE!  There are more ways on our website. Check it out!1. Stroll through the California Botanic Garden. There are FREE admission days 4-5 times a year. They also offer free admission year `round through several other programs including Museums for All (free for SNAP/EBT recipients) and the LA County Library`s Discover and Go pass program (free for library card holders)2. The First Sunday Family-Friendly Bird Walks from 8 am to 10 am; a relaxing two hour stroll.3. A self guided mural tour - vibrant murals created by local artists.4. The Farmers & Artisans Market is every Sunday 8am to 1pm and the vibe is fantastic! Live music, people watching  and fresh produce!5. Free Family Day at the Claremont Lewis Museum of Art; inspire those artistic talents!6. Go on a Claremont College campus tour. Check out the architecture, gardens and art installations.7. The Folk Music Center has regular events and jam sessions. We love their free Saturday night events!8. The Padua Hills Theatre grounds hold art shows and bridal exhibitions or bring a picnic and enjoy the beautiful surroundings.9. In the heart of Claremont Village, every Friday night is Friday Nights LIVE! Free live music at 3 venues; it\u2019s like a mini festival!10. The streets of Claremont will soon play host to the Village Venture, October 26th. There\u2019s a free children\u2019s Halloween costume parade and over 450 vendors.Check out more FREE things to do in Claremont on our website and SAVE this post!@visitclaremont @californiabotanicgarden @claremontheritage @claremontchamber @claremontfarmersmarket @pomonacollege @claremont_lmoa @theclaremontforum @paduaweddings @scrippscollege @folkmusiccenter @village_venture...1213visitclaremontViewSep 30OpenMark your calendars for the 42nd Annual Village Venture Arts & Crafts Festival on Saturday, October 26, 2024, from 9 AM to 5 PM in the heart of Claremont Village! \ud83c\udf42\ud83c\udfa8\u2728 This beloved community event is back and better than ever, bringing together over 500 artists, crafters, and makers to showcase their unique creations. Whether you`re a longtime local or a first-time visitor, the Village Venture is the perfect way to experience the creative spirit of Claremont.Stroll through the charming, tree-lined streets as you explore a diverse array of handmade goods, from stunning jewelry and one-of-a-kind artwork to cozy knitwear and intricate woodcrafts. It\u2019s the perfect opportunity to pick up early holiday gifts or find something special just for yourself. The festival also features live entertainment, delicious food vendors, and a dedicated children\u2019s area with fun activities for the little ones.As you enjoy the vibrant atmosphere, take a moment to soak in the fall season\u2019s beauty and the welcoming community vibe that makes Claremont Village so special. Whether you\u2019re here to shop, eat, or enjoy a day out with family and friends, the Village Venture promises a day full of inspiration and joy. Everyone has a great time!Don\u2019t miss out on this annual tradition\u2014see you at the Claremont Village on October 26th! \ud83c\udf83\ud83c\udf41...584Load More...Follow on Instagram"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Looking for the perfect weekend getaway? Head to Claremont, CA! \ud83c\udf89 Bring your friends, family, and even your pups for an unforgettable adventure. Start by exploring the historic Claremont Packing House with its cool shops and restaurants. Play retro games at Lost Levels and catch a film at Laemmle\u2019s Claremont! \ud83c\udfae\ud83c\udf7fPick up goodies from The Cheese Cave and enjoy a picnic at the serene California Botanic Garden. Don`t miss the Claremont Lewis Museum of Art in the charming Claremont Depot. For meals, enjoy lunch al fresco at the Claremont Village Square and indulge in incredible dinners at Bardot or Union on Yale. \ud83c\udf7d\ufe0fOn Sunday, shop local at the Farmers & Artisans Market. With free parking and the option to take the Metrolink straight to the village, getting around is a breeze. So, what are you waiting for? Book your fun-filled weekend in Claremont now! \ud83d\udecd\ufe0f\ud83c\udf3f\u2728#claremontca  #weekendgetaway  #travelwithfriends #dogfriendlytravel #exploreclaremont #shareclaremont #visitclaremont #socaladventures Best Things TO Do in Claremont, CA -  Weekend Getaway to Claremont - Where to eat and what to do in Claremont, California@uniononyale @bardotclaremont @lostlevelsclaremont @claremontpackinghouse @claremontfarmersmarket @californiabotanicgarden @claremontcheese @laemmleclaremont..."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Fall in love with Claremont on a beautiful autumn day, where the crisp air and vibrant foliage set the perfect stage for romance and adventure. \ud83c\udf42\u2764\ufe0f Hop on a bike and ride through the picturesque campuses of the Claremont Colleges, where tree-lined paths and stunning architecture create a postcard-worthy backdrop. Or take a Lyft to the Webb Schools campus to check out fossils at the Alf Museum.For a truly magical moment, catch the sunrise at James Turrells`s Skyspace, \"Dividing The LIght\", where the early morning light dances through his architectural masterpiece, filling the space with ethereal colors. As the day unfolds, head to Ironbark Ciderworks for a refreshing cider\u2014perfectly crafted from local ingredients and brimming with fall flavors.Spend the afternoon shopping in Claremont Village, where you\u2019ll find everything from unique boutiques to cozy bookstores. As evening approaches, dine at one of Claremont\u2019s cutest cafes, where delicious food and a charming atmosphere make for a perfect meal.End your day by watching the sunset in the nearby mountains, where the sky turns shades of orange and pink, casting a warm glow over the landscape. Whether you\u2019re here for a romantic getaway or to soak in the season`s beauty, Claremont offers a day full of moments to fall in love with. \ud83c\udf05\ud83d\udeb4\u200d\u2642\ufe0f\ud83c\udf41#claremontca #claremontcalifornia #visitclaremont #discoverclaremontThings to do in Claremont * Claremont in the fall * Claremont in Autumn..."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "\ud83c\udf83\ud83d\udc7b Spooky season is in full swing in Claremont, and the Halloween vibes are stronger than ever! From spine-chilling thrills to festive fun, October in Claremont brings all the spooky magic we love.Past years have been filled with memorable moments (let`s take a quick look)! We loved celebrating D\u00eda de los Muertos at Rio de Ojas, getting into the Halloween spirit with Aromatique Skin and Body Care and finding mystical treasures at Buddhamouse Emporium. \ud83d\udd6f\ufe0f\u2728We never forget to stop by SMELL in the Claremont Packing House for all things sweet and eerie, and hopefully it is happening again this year, but if you get a chance, explore the haunted beauty of the California Botanic Garden\u2019s Bootanical Family Night Walk! Check their calendar for other fun happenings, as they are constantly creating new events.\ud83c\udf3f\ud83c\udf83 And of course, no October is complete without the Village Venture, where costumes, crafts, and chills come together for a thrilling good time. \ud83d\udc7b\ud83c\udf42Happening October 26th all day!Things to do in Claremont * Claremont experiences * Family friendly Claremont * Claremont in October * Halloween * Village Venture * Family Fun#HalloweenInClaremont #ClaremontSpookySeason #VillageVenture #DiaDeLosMuertos #BootanicalNight #OctoberVibes..."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Top FREE Things to do in Claremont, California \u2b50\ufe0fSAVE this post for your next visit!It\u2019s true, the best things in life are free! There is no shortage of free things to do in the beautiful, tree-filled, hidden gem of Claremont.Here are ten ways to enjoy your visit, TOTALLY FREE!  There are more ways on our website. Check it out!1. Stroll through the California Botanic Garden. There are FREE admission days 4-5 times a year. They also offer free admission year `round through several other programs including Museums for All (free for SNAP/EBT recipients) and the LA County Library`s Discover and Go pass program (free for library card holders)2. The First Sunday Family-Friendly Bird Walks from 8 am to 10 am; a relaxing two hour stroll.3. A self guided mural tour - vibrant murals created by local artists.4. The Farmers & Artisans Market is every Sunday 8am to 1pm and the vibe is fantastic! Live music, people watching  and fresh produce!5. Free Family Day at the Claremont Lewis Museum of Art; inspire those artistic talents!6. Go on a Claremont College campus tour. Check out the architecture, gardens and art installations.7. The Folk Music Center has regular events and jam sessions. We love their free Saturday night events!8. The Padua Hills Theatre grounds hold art shows and bridal exhibitions or bring a picnic and enjoy the beautiful surroundings.9. In the heart of Claremont Village, every Friday night is Friday Nights LIVE! Free live music at 3 venues; it\u2019s like a mini festival!10. The streets of Claremont will soon play host to the Village Venture, October 26th. There\u2019s a free children\u2019s Halloween costume parade and over 450 vendors.Check out more FREE things to do in Claremont on our website and SAVE this post!@visitclaremont @californiabotanicgarden @claremontheritage @claremontchamber @claremontfarmersmarket @pomonacollege @claremont_lmoa @theclaremontforum @paduaweddings @scrippscollege @folkmusiccenter @village_venture..."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Accomplishments (Faculty and Staff)"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty Employment Opportunities"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Institutional Research, Office of"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "The mission of the Pomona College Women\u2019s Union is to secure positive changes for women in their personal and political lives and to work toward deconstructing gender-based constraints within both local and global contexts. We will engage The Claremont Colleges while extending our reach into our surrounding communities. The Women\u2019s Union is committed to providing space and programming involving all genders, tailored to the diverse needs of women. In order to fulfill these commitments, we will exercise an active position against interlocking systems of oppression based on, but not limited to, race, ethnicity, sex, gender, sexual orientation, class, religion, and ability."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "For more information on events or to contact us, visit ourFacebook pageor emailpomonawomensunion@gmail.com."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Jasmine Holt \u201925(they/them) is an Asian-American, queer college student from Minnesota where they had the opportunity to foster their passion for book arts, music, and other forms of creative self-expression as a means to organize and connect with their community. Majoring in Media Studies and Art, they have been able to further explore how art, design, and education can be utilized as a radical tool for restorative justice on campus. Holt is excited to be a Head Coordinator to continue organizing empathetic workshops centered around community healing and uplifting marginalized voices"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Student OrganizationsCollegiateLink Club SearchModel UNPeer Mentoring GroupsFLI Scholars at PomonaThe Women's UnionHistory of the Women's Union"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Women's UnionHistory of the Women's Union"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Claremont Colleges Chapter of Sigma Xi elects juniors and seniors to associate membership on the basis of outstanding aptitude in science as demonstrated by participation in research."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The honors cum laude, magna cum laude, and summa cum laude are awarded on the basis of the overall grade point average of the student's work. The faculty has limited graduation honors to the top quarter of the graduating class."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "TheMaryFordBaconMemorialPrizes. Three prizes for the best essays or monographs relating to the Constitution of the United States are awarded annually by the Economics, History, and Politics departments. The Mary Ford Bacon Memorial Fund also provides a sum of money for the purchase of books and other materials on the Constitution recommended by the faculty in Economics, History, and Politics."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "TheTedGleasonAward. An award established by the family of Edward Rowse Gleason '70 is given annually to a man or woman student who has made a warm-hearted contribution to the community life of the College through such traits as sympathy, friendliness, good cheer, generosity, and, particularly, perseverance and courage."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Mark Syverson Memorial Book Prize. Endowedby the Syverson family and friends, this prize honors the memory of Mark Syverson, long-time Office of Admissions staff member who died in 1998. The recipient of this prize is an incoming first-year student selected by the Admissions staff."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Matthew Klopfleisch Prize in Art. Endowed by Stephanie '62 and Randall Klopfleisch in memory of their son Matthew Klopfleisch '99 who died in 1997, this prize is awarded annually to a student chosen by the Art Department faculty for excellence in art."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Louisa Moseley Fine Arts Prizes. Two prizes are awarded annually, one for an outstanding senior project in studio art and one for an outstanding senior thesis in art history."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Rembrandt Club Junior Art Prize. Awarded by the Rembrandt Club, a community group dedicated to the fine arts, this prize is awarded to a junior art student for travel to art collections or sites of special significance for a junior art project, or for research during the summer after the junior year. Grants are also possible for purchase of materials or research resources related to development as a major."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Stanley D. Wilson Prize. A prize endowed by Dr. Stanley D. Wilson is awarded annually to the student whose independent study and research show the greatest promise for creative work."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "The F.S. Jennings Memorial Prizes.Prizes are awarded each year for excellence in English. In awarding these prizes, special consideration is given to freshman students who make persistent and successful efforts to improve the quality of their written English and to majors in English literature whose critical writing is adjudged to be distinguished. Unusually fine performance in writing may be awarded wherever it is found."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Frederick L. Mulhauser Memorial Award. A prize in memory of Frederick L. Mulhauser, Professor of English from 1941 to 1974, is given to one or more students studying in England under the guidance of the Pomona English faculty, on the basis of interest and excellence in the study of English literature."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Jane Jacobs Thesis Award in Environmental Analysis.This award recognizes an outstanding senior thesis that is focused on sustainability and the built environment and that might address such questions of architecture and the human landscape, climate change, transportation, toxics and waste, urban planning and design, among others."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "THE TONI CLARK PRIZE IN GENDER AND WOMEN'S STUDIESThis prize was established in 1974 and initially named The Commission on the Education of Women President\u2019s Prize in Gender and Women\u2019s Studies to encourage original scholarly and creative work by students on the topic of women in all fields of the curriculum. To commemorate Professor Emeritus of English, Associate Dean of Students, and Dean of Women Toni Clark\u2019s contributions to Gender and Women\u2019s Studies, then-President David Oxtoby renamed the prize in her honor after she passed away in 2016. One or two awards will be made to the best entry(ies) on a thesis relating to gender and women\u2019s studies."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The D.B. McIntyre-H. Stanton Hill Award.Established by H. Stanton Hill '33 and his wife, Mary C. Hill, to honor the contributions of Donald B. McIntyre, Professor of Geology from 1954 to 1989, to the Pomona College Geology Department. The award is given to an outstanding student in any field of the geological sciences, at the discretion of the department faculty."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The John Hayes Beaver History Prize.One or more prizes are awarded annually to first-, second-, or third-year students who have demonstrated integrity in their actions and perseverance in their work."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Ada F. Hartog Memorial Prize in History.A fund established by John A. Hartog '74 in honor of his mother provides an award each year to a graduating senior in the Department of History who has shown outstanding intellectual achievement in the field of European history."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The John H. Kemble Senior Thesis Award in History.A prize in honor of John H. Kemble, Professor of History from 1936 to 1977, is given for the best senior thesis, judged on research and presentation. It is awarded only in those years when there are at least three deserving entries in the competition."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Vincent Learnihan Western Civilization Prize.Established by former students of Vincent Learnihan, Professor of History from 1949 to 1982, this prize is awarded to a first-year student chosen by History instructors."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Eda May Haskell Library Prize. Awarded for the best library submitted by a senior student, not necessarily for the largest or most expensive collection but for the most intelligently selected books in one or more fields of the student's interest. Endowed by John H. Kemble, Professor of History from 1936 to 1977."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Bruce Jay Levy Prize in Mathematics. This prize is awarded annually to a student chosen by the Mathematics Department faculty for excellence in the field of mathematics."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Scott Winslow Award in Media Studies.An award endowed in 1996 by Anne Shaw Price '44 and Nicholas Winslow '64, both members of the Pomona College Board of Trustees, in memory of Benjamin Scott Winslow (1972-1989). Awarded annually to a Media Studies major whose senior thesis or senior project is deemed the most outstanding of that year by the program faculty."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Philip Goldberg Memorial Prize. Awarded annually to a Pomona student, preferably a senior string player, for outstanding instrumental performance, in memory of the dedicated violist and teacher whose service on the faculty was cut short by untimely death."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Rudolph Polk Memorial Award. Established in 1957 by friends and colleagues of Rudolph Polk, this award is given to a student in instrumental music (violin, viola, cello, or piano) on the basis of technical competence, musicianship, and general musical background. Students of any of The Claremont Colleges are eligible. The program is administered by Scripps College through an intercollegiate faculty committee."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Lorn S. Foster Prize in Race and Politics\u2013this cash prize, endowed by a gift in honor of Lorn S. Foster, Professor of Politics from 1978 to 2018, is awarded annually to the outstanding senior in the field of Race and Politics. The awardee is selected by the Politics faculty, but is not restricted to Politics majors"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Iberian Grant.A prize established by Jeronimo Arango, Jr., is awarded annually to one or two students for summer research in Spain on some aspect of Spanish history, economics, politics, or international relations."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Classes are small, so students and faculty can build close relationships, delve into research and explore across academic fields. More than half of all Pomona students work closely with professors in research projects, receiving academic and financial support for a deeper approach to learning."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "WATCH: Faculty and Student Research"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "More than 90% of our students live on campus here in Southern California all four years, and many professors live within five miles of campus. New collaborations or discussions can spring up anywhere \u2013 a residence hall, club meeting or at lunch with a professor."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The takeover of Carnegie Hall and the events that ensued should be unfathomable in a close-knit, ethical, and caring learning community such as ours. Our academic mission was directly targeted. Faculty, students, staff, and high-school student visitors were subjected to intimidation and fear. This is unacceptable."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "I am grateful to the members of our community who, in the midst of crisis, have stood up for who we are at our best. My deepest appreciation to the campus safety staff who stayed with other members of our community throughout the day; to the student affairs staff who worked to de-escalate the situation and to bring help; to the faculty, staff and students who helped others evacuate the building; to the faculty from around campus and the leadership of CGU, who answered the call to provide classroom and office space for displaced faculty; to the members of ASPC who held a letter-writing campaign offering support to Carnegie faculty and staff; to the facilities and ITS staff who have labored to restore the building; and to the staff, faculty, and students who have worked to find a path that is true to who we are: Thank you."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "I grieve, alongside so many of you, thatthe destruction in Carnegie Hall was extensiveand the harm to individuals and our mission was so great. I want you all to know that, based on our extensive but still growing inquiry,the vast majority of those who occupied Carnegie are not Pomona students. Starting this week, disciplinary letters are going out to students from Pomona and the other Claremont Colleges who have been identified as taking part in the takeover of Carnegie Hall. Student groups affiliated with this incident are also under investigation. Individuals who are not students will be banned from our campus. Additional evidence is still under review. It is important that everyone understand that Pomona is committed to the integrity of our disciplinary processes, and we will be unable to comment on individual cases. I anticipate that, within the scope of the student code, and commensurate with individual circumstances, sanctions will range widely, including campus bans, suspension and expulsion\u2014a step we do not take lightly. As always, we have due process on our campus, with opportunities for appeal."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Every Sagehen, as the executive committee of our faculty so eloquently wrote, has a role to play in rebuilding our sense of collective responsibility, and in finding a path forward that restores our community."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "To Contact President Starr for a Media Interview:"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Boston Globe,Widen the College Pipeline So That Talent Everywhere Can Succeed Anywhere, October 27, 2022"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "If this error continues, pleasecontact JSTOR support."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Popular topics:Need Help Logging in to JSTOR?Using JSTOR to Start Your ResearchHow to Register & Get Free Access to Content"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Accessing JSTORFind support for getting access to content on JSTOR through your institution or as an independent researcher."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Find support for getting access to content on JSTOR through your institution or as an independent researcher."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Organizing and Presenting ResearchLearn how to save, share, present, and teach with what you find on JSTOR with Workspace."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Organizing and Presenting Research"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Teaching ResourcesResources for librarians, educators, and faculty to assist with teaching using JSTOR."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Resources for librarians, educators, and faculty to assist with teaching using JSTOR."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/contact"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Ninety-four percent of our students live on campus all four years, and many\u00a0professors live within five miles of campus. This creates a close-knit community where new collaborations or eye-opening discussions can spring up anywhere \u2013 a dorm, club meeting, or at lunch with a professor."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "If you consider our campus a hub, we have some pretty amazing spokes: The Claremont Colleges\u00a0has more than 6,000+ students you can meet through 250+ clubs and 2,000+ classes. We\u2019re nestled in Southern California, a natural and cultural playground you can explore on day trips, field trips and internships. You may even take your Pomona experience global with study abroad or international research and internships."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Concerts and recitalsby students, faculty and guest artists"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona offers students with a variety of opportunities to develop their leadership skills in the areas of student government, student-run groups, residence hall and sponsors, outdoor education, academic research, community service projects, peer counseling, on-campus jobs and off-campus internships \u2013 and much more."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "working at the Museum, Admissions Office, or in Athletics,"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Students can look for jobs usingHandshake via our Career Development Office. For more information on student employment and work allotments at Pomona, visit ourjobs page in Financial Aid."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Our students have interned everywhere from the U.S. federal government and PricewaterhouseCoopers to Warner Brothers Records and UNAIDS."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Sustainability is in our classrooms too. Through ourEnvironmental Analysis program, students can explore a wide variety of issues, from the science side of things to environmental justice, history, or the built environment. Even if you\u2019re not an EA major, one of these classes can fulfill your general education (we call them \u201cbreadth of study\u201d) requirements."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "In Fall 2006, Pomona College President David Oxtoby established the President's Advisory Committee on Sustainability (PACS). The committee consists of faculty, staff, and students and meets biweekly during the academic year. This committee is responsible for:"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "For more information about attending a PACS meeting or being a part of PACS, or if you would like more information about the sustainability fund, contactsustainability@pomona.edu"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "reduction in GHG emissions. 2030 Goal: Carbon Neutrality with a 50% reduction in energy emissions. (Updated: July 2023)"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Why are you passionate about sustainability?I'm passionate about sustainability education and literacy as a mode of empowerment to galvanize collective youth action to help address the climate crisis!"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Quality Thrift StoreAddress: 4433 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United StatesTransportation: 1 hour walk, 35 minute bus ride, 10 minute car rideBest for: absolutely everything!"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4433 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4433 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Three Way Thrift StoreAddress: 10152 Central Ave Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United StatesTransportation: 1 hour walk, 45 minute bus ride, 12 minute car rideBest for: clothes and furniture"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 10152 Central Ave Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 10152 Central Ave Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Great Savings Thrift StoreAddress: 4615 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United StatesTransportation: 1 hour walk, 32 minute bus ride, 11 minute car rideBest for: shoes and clothesTip: visit Quality, Three Way, and Great Savings Thrift on the same day as they are all within walking distance of one another. On Saturdays all three stores usually have a 30% discount off the entire store and 20% student discounts on Wednesdays."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4615 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4615 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "ACTS Thrift StoreAddress: 232 E Foothill Blvd Pomona, CA\u00a0 91767 United StatesTransportation: 50 minute walk, 28 minute bus ride, 9 minute car rideBest for: absolutely everything! Bonus: there is a Goodwill one store over, not even a two minute walk away!"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 232 E Foothill Blvd Pomona, CA\u00a0 91767 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 232 E Foothill Blvd Pomona, CA\u00a0 91767 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Community Thrift StoreAddress: 19720 Arrow Hwy Covina, CA 91724 United StatesTransportation: 50 minute bike ride, 50 minute bus ride, 20 minute car rideBest for: clothes, clothes, and more clothes! This is by far the largest thrift store for clothing, shoes, and jewelry in the area."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 19720 Arrow Hwy Covina, CA 91724 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 19720 Arrow Hwy Covina, CA 91724 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Eco Thrift StoreAddress: 1190 S Garey Ave Pomona, CA\u00a0 91766 United StatesTransportation: 30 minute bike ride, 40 minute bus ride, 16 minute car rideBest for: home goods and furniture. Be sure to also check out the antique mall and vintage stores in the same area (downtown Pomona)."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 1190 S Garey Ave Pomona, CA\u00a0 91766 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 1190 S Garey Ave Pomona, CA\u00a0 91766 United States"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "We'd like to feature Cecilia Muecke and her awesome work at the Pomona Farm! The Farm is a working farm available for the college community to find their personal connection to the environment. The sustainably grown food at the Farm gets donated to the community and organizations like the Uncommon Good nonprofit. Cecilia Muecke (PO '25) got involved with the Farm by volunteering during her first semester at Pomona. Since then, she has been involved at the Farm in various capacities. She spent her sophomore summer doing a Summer Undergraduate Research Program fellowship at the Farm. Cecilia is now a Farm Assistant at the Pomona Organic Farm and co-leads the Farm Club! In Cecilia\u2019s eyes, the Farm is \u201call about getting people outside, connecting with themselves, each other, and the land.\u201dBy collaborating with her, we were able to host our \"Freshman Flock to the Farm\" event, where we made pizzas! See below!"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "There are many other exciting developments at the farm. Farm Manager Jill Gomez and Student Compost Drivers are working hard for the Farm and take \u201ca leadership role in composting all of Pomona's food waste as [the Farm] transition[s] away from industrial composting.\u201d\u00a0Another Farm Club member, Anna Parrott, is planning a spirit-building event for students and EA faculty at the farm on November 16th from 4:15-6:15 pm with a regathering at 7:30. The purpose of this event, called Collective Horizons, is to discuss and envision hope in a future with climate change. After dinner, attendees will regather around a campfire at 7:30 to tell campfire stories, poems, and enjoy s\u2019mores!"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Dr. Kim TallBear, Professor, Faculty of Native Studies, University of Alberta"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Canada Research Chair (CRC) in Indigenous Peoples, Technoscience, and Society | Thursday, November 9, 4:15 PM in Hahn 101"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Kim TallBear (Sisseton-Wahpeton Oyate) (she/her) is Professor and Canada Research Chair in Indigenous Peoples, Technoscience, and Society, Faculty of Native Studies, University of Alberta. She is the author of Native American DNA: Tribal Belonging and the False Promise of Genetic Science. In addition to studying genome science disruptions to Indigenous self-definitions, Dr. TallBear studies colonial disruptions to Indigenous sexual relations. She is a regular panelist on the weekly podcast, Media Indigena. You can follow her research group at https://indigenoussts.com/. She tweets @KimTallBear. You can also follow her monthly posts on her Substack newsletter, Unsettle: Indigenous affairs, cultural politics & (de)colonization."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Campus Climate Network is revitalizing the student climate movement. They aim to build an international coalition of student-led climate justice groups fighting to cut ties with the fossil fuel industry and its enablers. They provide students with the training, resources, and connections they need to run winning campaigns on campus and become the next generation of climate justice leaders.https://actionnetwork.org/forms/get-involved-with-fossil-free-research/"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Quality Thrift StoreAddress: 4433 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United StatesTransportation: 1 hour walk, 35 minute bus ride, 10 minute car rideBest for: absolutely everything!"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4433 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4433 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Three Way Thrift StoreAddress: 10152 Central Ave Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United StatesTransportation: 1 hour walk, 45 minute bus ride, 12 minute car rideBest for: clothes and furniture"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 10152 Central Ave Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 10152 Central Ave Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Great Savings Thrift StoreAddress: 4615 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United StatesTransportation: 1 hour walk, 32 minute bus ride, 11 minute car rideBest for: shoes and clothesTip: visit Quality, Three Way, and Great Savings Thrift on the same day as they are all within walking distance of one another. On Saturdays all three stores usually have a 30% discount off the entire store and 20% student discounts on Wednesdays."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4615 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 4615 Holt Blvd Montclair, CA\u00a0 91763 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "ACTS Thrift StoreAddress: 232 E Foothill Blvd Pomona, CA\u00a0 91767 United StatesTransportation: 50 minute walk, 28 minute bus ride, 9 minute car rideBest for: absolutely everything! Bonus: there is a Goodwill one store over, not even a two minute walk away!"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 232 E Foothill Blvd Pomona, CA\u00a0 91767 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 232 E Foothill Blvd Pomona, CA\u00a0 91767 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Community Thrift StoreAddress: 19720 Arrow Hwy Covina, CA 91724 United StatesTransportation: 50 minute bike ride, 50 minute bus ride, 20 minute car rideBest for: clothes, clothes, and more clothes! This is by far the largest thrift store for clothing, shoes, and jewelry in the area."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 19720 Arrow Hwy Covina, CA 91724 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 19720 Arrow Hwy Covina, CA 91724 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Eco Thrift StoreAddress: 1190 S Garey Ave Pomona, CA\u00a0 91766 United StatesTransportation: 30 minute bike ride, 40 minute bus ride, 16 minute car rideBest for: home goods and furniture. Be sure to also check out the antique mall and vintage stores in the same area (downtown Pomona)."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 1190 S Garey Ave Pomona, CA\u00a0 91766 United States"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address: 1190 S Garey Ave Pomona, CA\u00a0 91766 United States"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "We'd like to feature Cecilia Muecke and her awesome work at the Pomona Farm! The Farm is a working farm available for the college community to find their personal connection to the environment. The sustainably grown food at the Farm gets donated to the community and organizations like the Uncommon Good nonprofit. Cecilia Muecke (PO '25) got involved with the Farm by volunteering during her first semester at Pomona. Since then, she has been involved at the Farm in various capacities. She spent her sophomore summer doing a Summer Undergraduate Research Program fellowship at the Farm. Cecilia is now a Farm Assistant at the Pomona Organic Farm and co-leads the Farm Club! In Cecilia\u2019s eyes, the Farm is \u201call about getting people outside, connecting with themselves, each other, and the land.\u201dBy collaborating with her, we were able to host our \"Freshman Flock to the Farm\" event, where we made pizzas! See below!"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "There are many other exciting developments at the farm. Farm Manager Jill Gomez and Student Compost Drivers are working hard for the Farm and take \u201ca leadership role in composting all of Pomona's food waste as [the Farm] transition[s] away from industrial composting.\u201d\u00a0Another Farm Club member, Anna Parrott, is planning a spirit-building event for students and EA faculty at the farm on November 16th from 4:15-6:15 pm with a regathering at 7:30. The purpose of this event, called Collective Horizons, is to discuss and envision hope in a future with climate change. After dinner, attendees will regather around a campfire at 7:30 to tell campfire stories, poems, and enjoy s\u2019mores!"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Dr. Kim TallBear, Professor, Faculty of Native Studies, University of Alberta"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Canada Research Chair (CRC) in Indigenous Peoples, Technoscience, and Society | Thursday, November 9, 4:15 PM in Hahn 101"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Kim TallBear (Sisseton-Wahpeton Oyate) (she/her) is Professor and Canada Research Chair in Indigenous Peoples, Technoscience, and Society, Faculty of Native Studies, University of Alberta. She is the author of Native American DNA: Tribal Belonging and the False Promise of Genetic Science. In addition to studying genome science disruptions to Indigenous self-definitions, Dr. TallBear studies colonial disruptions to Indigenous sexual relations. She is a regular panelist on the weekly podcast, Media Indigena. You can follow her research group at https://indigenoussts.com/. She tweets @KimTallBear. You can also follow her monthly posts on her Substack newsletter, Unsettle: Indigenous affairs, cultural politics & (de)colonization."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Campus Climate Network is revitalizing the student climate movement. They aim to build an international coalition of student-led climate justice groups fighting to cut ties with the fossil fuel industry and its enablers. They provide students with the training, resources, and connections they need to run winning campaigns on campus and become the next generation of climate justice leaders.https://actionnetwork.org/forms/get-involved-with-fossil-free-research/"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "\u201cI gave my first gift to Pomona as a first-year. Working as a caller for the Annual Fund, I knew participation was key to the success of the program. I also give because of the generous financial aid I receive.\u201d"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Last day of classes for spring semester; last day to enroll in a summer research/reading course; last day to petition for an incomplete"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Last day of classes for spring semester; last day to enroll in a summer research/reading course; last day to petition for an incomplete"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College Dining Services\u00a0is proudly self-operated by Pomona employees for Pomona College.\u00a0Our staff is committed to offering\u00a0a top-notch dining\u00a0experience\u00a0for all of\u00a0our students, staff and faculty.\u00a0We are committed to sustainability, healthy eating and overall excellence in all aspects of the dining experience."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Currently, only meal plans or Claremont Cash is accepted during the Summer.\u00a0 Meal plans are available to students, staff, and faculty.Please view more about prices here."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Residential students will have a meal plan that will provide expanded service hours and unlimited access at Frary, Frank Dining Hall, as well as access to the Coop Fountain and Caf\u00e9 47.Menushave also been expanded to provide more vegan and vegetarian options, as well as choices that address allergy concerns. The Coop Fountain will be the site of the Late-Night Snack Program creating a central hub for student activity, Tuesdays through Thursdays."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "If you have additional questions, please contact Jose Martinez, dining services General Manager atjose.martinez@pomona.edu."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The dining halls feature a number of private dining rooms (PDRs) that allow students, faculty and staff to convene groups of up to 20(room capacities vary)during meal times for meetings. The Frank Dining Hall Blue Room can accommodate up to 99 guests with a minimum of 35 guests. All PDR reservations, including Frank Blue Room, may only be requested during normal dining hall meal periods and require a dining hall meal to be purchased either by a meal swipe."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Students may request the use of PDRs through Engage and faculty and staff may request the use of PDRs through the EMS Web App.Submission of a request does not guarantee approval."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Food sensitivity (also known as delayed food allergy) is quite another story. Delayed reactions manifest in many different ways as they can affect any organ system in the body and can take from 45 minutes to several days for symptoms to become apparent. The delayed onset of symptoms and complex physiological mechanisms involved in food sensitivities make them an especially difficult puzzle to try to solve either on your own or with most laboratory serum tests. In fact, food sensitivities often go undiagnosed or misdiagnosed. The treatments prescribed usually provide only temporary relief that mask the symptoms instead of addressing the root cause of the problems."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Liz is thrilled to be a part of the Dining Services team as your nutrition guidance counselor. While ensuring there are nutritious and delicious foods available every day, she would also like to help you make healthier choices. Available for one-on-one nutrition counseling (free of charge to students!), she is happy to discuss specific health needs or goals.\u00a0 She will work with you to develop strategies to implement a reasonable plan that works for you and compliments your lifestyle. Throughout the year, Liz will offer workshops on topics such as general nutrition, health information, nutrition for athletes, vegetarianism, weight and obesity, heart health, organic foods and cooking."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "TheHealthy Eating Plate, created by nutrition experts at Harvard School of Public Health and editors at Harvard Health Publications, was designed to address deficiencies in the U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA)\u2019s MyPlate. The Healthy Eating Plate provides detailed guidance, in a simple format, to help people make the best eating choices."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "When it comes to dietary fat, what matters most is the type of fat you eat. Contrary to past dietary advice promotinglow-fat diets, newer research shows that healthy fats are necessary and beneficial for health."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "One of the most widely used tools for estimating excess fat is the body mass index (BMI). BMI only measures excess weight, calculating a ratio of one\u2019s weight to height. [4] However, research has shown that BMI often correlates with \u201cgold standard\u201d direct measures of fat mass and fat-free mass such as underwater weighing (hydrostatic weighing) and dual X-ray absorptiometry (DEXA). In comparison with these methods that require expensive equipment, BMI is noninvasive, easy to calculate, and can be used anywhere."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Because of its simplicity and widespread use, BMI is often used when studying populations. Researchers can compare the BMI of groups of people over time in different areas, to screen for obesity and its related health risks."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "BMI does have several limitations. It can\u2019t measure location of fat (e.g., belly fat is linked with greater health risks), muscle mass, or bone mass\u2014all of which contribute to weight. One\u2019s age, sex, race, and ethnicity can also affect BMI. [4] For example, when comparing two people with the same BMI:"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "At a population level, a high BMI is generally associated with an increased risk of disease and early death. Many studies have shown that a BMI above 25 increases the chances of dying early compared to those with normal weight:A meta-analysis published in theNew England Journal of Medicineshowed a clear relationship between BMI and mortality, where both people with underweight (BMI <18.5) and with overweight and obesity (BMI >25) had greater mortality. [7] The lowest death rate from any cause was associated with the BMI range between 22.5 and 24.9. To address some methodological flaws in previous studies, this study excluded smokers who tend to have lower weight due to smoking, individuals with cancer and heart disease who might have lost weight due to these conditions, and individuals over the age of 85 who could have a normal BMI but suffer from frailty or other age-related unhealthy weight loss.Another large meta-analysis inThe Lancetthat looked at data across four continents found that for every five units higher of a BMI above 25, risk of premature death increased by about 31%. [8] The study also looked at specific causes of death, and found that for each 5-unit increase in BMI above 25, the corresponding increases in risk were 49% for cardiovascular mortality, 38% for respiratory disease mortality, and 19% for cancer mortality. This meta-analysis also excluded participants who were current or former smokers, those who had chronic diseases at the beginning of the study, and any who died in the first five years of follow-up (a combined 1.6 million deaths were recorded across these studies where participants were followed for an average of 14 years)."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "A meta-analysis published in theNew England Journal of Medicineshowed a clear relationship between BMI and mortality, where both people with underweight (BMI <18.5) and with overweight and obesity (BMI >25) had greater mortality. [7] The lowest death rate from any cause was associated with the BMI range between 22.5 and 24.9. To address some methodological flaws in previous studies, this study excluded smokers who tend to have lower weight due to smoking, individuals with cancer and heart disease who might have lost weight due to these conditions, and individuals over the age of 85 who could have a normal BMI but suffer from frailty or other age-related unhealthy weight loss."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Another large meta-analysis inThe Lancetthat looked at data across four continents found that for every five units higher of a BMI above 25, risk of premature death increased by about 31%. [8] The study also looked at specific causes of death, and found that for each 5-unit increase in BMI above 25, the corresponding increases in risk were 49% for cardiovascular mortality, 38% for respiratory disease mortality, and 19% for cancer mortality. This meta-analysis also excluded participants who were current or former smokers, those who had chronic diseases at the beginning of the study, and any who died in the first five years of follow-up (a combined 1.6 million deaths were recorded across these studies where participants were followed for an average of 14 years)."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "When examining the relationship between BMI and mortality, failure to adjust for these variables can lead to reverse causation (where a low body weight is the result of underlying illness, rather than the cause) or confounding by smoking (because smokers tend to weigh less than non-smokers and have much higher mortality rates). Experts say these methodological flaws have led to paradoxical, misleading results that suggest a survival advantage to being overweight."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Some researchers consider waist circumference to be a better measure of unhealthy body fat than BMI as it addresses visceral abdominal fat, which is associated with metabolic problems, inflammation, and insulin resistance. [3,9] It is a good predictor of disease risk and early mortality, and provides a clearer picture of health, as abdominal fat can increase even if total weight remains the same. An increasing waist size can be an important \u201cwarning sign\u201d that prompts a closer look at potentially unhealthy lifestyle habits. In people who do not have overweight, increasing waist size over time may be an even more telling warning sign of increased health risks than BMI alone. [5,10]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Waist-to-height ratio (WHtR) is a simple, inexpensive screening tool that measures visceral abdominal fat. It has been supported by research to predict cardiometabolic risk factors such as hypertension, and early death, even when BMI falls within a healthy range. [15,16] When the waist circumference is less than half one\u2019s height, it is considered lower risk."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Individuals are weighed on dry land and then again while submerged in a water tank. [17] Researchers use formulas to estimate body volume, body density, and body fat percentage. Fat \u201cfloats\u201d with more buoyancy (less density) than water, so someone with high body fat will have a lower body density than someone with low body fat and more muscle. In other words, if one\u2019s weight under water is heavier than on land due to more muscle mass and less fat, this indicates a lower body fat percentage (and visa versa). This method is accurate but costly and typically only used in a research setting. It can cause discomfort as individuals must completely submerge under water including the head, and then exhale completely before obtaining the reading."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Individuals drink isotope-labeled water and give body fluid samples. Researchers analyze these samples for isotope levels, which are then used to calculate total body water, fat-free body mass, and in turn, body fat mass. [17] It is accurate, not as costly, and can be used in individuals with a BMI of 40 or higher, but accuracy can be decreased by illness, dehydration, or weight loss."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "X-ray beams pass through different body tissues at different rates. DEXA uses two low-level X-ray beams to develop estimates of fat-free mass, fat mass, and bone mineral density. [17] DEXA is accurate but uses heavy expensive equipment so is typically only used in research settings. It cannot distinguish between subcutaneous and visceral fat, cannot be used in persons sensitive to radiation (e.g., pregnant women, children), and cannot accommodate persons with a BMI of 35 or higher."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "These two imaging techniques are now considered to be the most accurate methods for measuring tissue, organ, and whole-body fat mass as well as lean muscle mass and bone mass. [17] It can measure specific body fat compartments, such as abdominal fat and subcutaneous fat. However, CT and MRI scans are typically used only in research settings because the equipment is extremely expensive and cannot be moved. CT scans cannot be used with pregnant women or children, due to exposure to ionizing radiation, and certain MRI and CT scanners may not be able to accommodate individuals with a BMI of 35 or higher."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Some studies suggest that the connection between body mass index and premature death follows a U-shaped curve. This means that weighing too much\u2014or too little\u2014isn\u2019t as healthy as weighing somewhere in the middle. The problem is that most of these studies included smokers and individuals with early, but undetected, chronic and fatal diseases. Cigarette smokers as a group weigh less than nonsmokers, in part because smoking deadens the appetite. Potentially deadly chronic diseases such as cancer, emphysema, kidney failure, and heart failure can cause weight loss even before they cause symptoms and have been diagnosed. So low weights don\u2019t necessarily cause early death. Instead, low weight is often the result of illnesses or habits that may be fatal."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Keszty\u00fcs D, Lampl J, Keszty\u00fcs T. The weight problem: overview of the most common concepts for body mass and fat distribution and critical consideration of their usefulness for risk assessment and practice.International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health. 2021 Oct 21;18(21):11070."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Clinical Guidelines on the Identification, Evaluation, and Treatment of Overweight and Obesity in Adults\u2013The Evidence Report. National Institutes of Health.Obesity Research. 1998 Sep;6 Suppl 2:51S-209S."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "As growing research and studies reveal the link between oral health and overall health, it becomes more evident that taking care of your teeth isn\u2019t just about having a nice smile and pleasant breath. Studies show that poor oral health is linked to heart disease, diabetes, pregnancy complications, and more, while positive oral health can enhance both mental and overall health. Good oral hygiene and regular visits to the dentist, combined with a healthy lifestyle and avoiding risks like excess sugar and smoking, help to keep your smile and body healthy."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Periodontal disease (gum disease)includes gingivitis and periodontitis. Gingivitis is the mildest form, in which the gums become red, swollen, and bleed easily. Gingivitis is reversible with professional treatment and good at-home oral care. If untreated, gingivitis can advance to periodontitis where chronic inflammation causes the tissues and bone that support the teeth to be damaged. Overtime, teeth can become loose and may fall out or need to be removed. [16]"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "It\u2019s only a semi-myth that eating carrots will help you see in the dark. A carrot\u2019s main nutrient, beta-carotene (responsible for this root vegetable\u2019s characteristic orange color), is a precursor to vitamin A and helps your eyes to adjust in dim conditions. Vitamin A can\u2019t give you superpowers of night vision or cure your dependence on contact lenses, but eating an adequate amount will support eye health."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Age-Related Eye Disease Study Research Group. A randomized, placebo-controlled, clinical trial of high-dose supplementation with vitamins C and E, beta carotene, and zinc for age-related macular degeneration and vision loss: AREDS report no. 8.Arch Ophthalmol. 2001;119(10):1417-1436."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Age-Related Eye Disease Study 2 Research Group. Lutein + zeaxanthin and omega-3 fatty acids for age-related macular degeneration: the Age-Related Eye Disease Study 2 (AREDS2) randomized clinical trial.JAMA. 2013 May 15;309(19):2005-15."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Randomized controlled trials in people who were at high risk for or who had heart disease at baseline.In the GISSI Prevention Trial, the results were mixed but mostly showed no preventive effects after more than three years of treatment with vitamin E among 11,000 heart attack survivors. [8] Results from the Heart Outcomes Prevention Evaluation (HOPE) trial also showed no benefit of four years\u2019 worth of vitamin E supplementation in more than 9,500 men and women already diagnosed with heart disease or at high risk for it. [9] In fact, when the HOPE trial was extended for another four years, researchers found that study volunteers who took vitamin E had a higher risk of heart failure. [10]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Randomized controlled trials in people without heart disease at baseline.The SU.VI.MAX randomized controlled trial found that seven years of low-dose vitamin E supplementation (as part of a daily antioxidant pill) reduced the risk of cancer and the risk of dying from any cause in men, but did not show these beneficial effects in women; the supplements did not offer any protection against heart disease in men or women. [12] Discouraging results have also come from the Physicians\u2019 Health Study II, an eight-year randomized controlled trial that involved nearly 15,000 middle-aged men, most of whom were free of heart disease at the start of the study. Researchers found that taking vitamin E supplements of 400 IU every other day, alone or with vitamin C, failed to offer any protection against heart attacks, strokes, or cardiovascular deaths. [13]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Investigators had hoped that the Selenium and Vitamin E Cancer Prevention Trial (SELECT) would give more definitive answers on vitamin E and prostate cancer. SELECT\u2019s 18,000 men were assigned to follow one of four pill regimens\u2014vitamin E plus selenium, vitamin E plus a selenium placebo, selenium plus a vitamin E placebo, or a double placebo\u2014and to be tracked for 7 to 12 years. But investigators halted the study halfway through in 2008 when early analyses showed that vitamin E offered no cancer or prostate cancer prevention benefit. [28] Though the trial ended, researchers continued to follow the men who had participated. In 2011, they reported a 17% higher risk of prostate cancer among men assigned to take vitamin E; there was no significant increased risk of prostate cancer among men who took vitamin E and selenium. [29]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Parkinson\u2019s Disease:Some, but not all, prospective studies suggest that getting higher intakes of vitamin E from diet\u2014not from high-dose supplements\u2014is associated with a reduced risk of Parkinson\u2019s disease. [43\u201345] In people who already have Parkinson\u2019s, high-dose vitamin E supplements do not slow the disease\u2019s progression. [46] Why the difference between vitamin E from foods versus that from supplements? It is possible that foods rich in vitamin E, such as nuts or legumes, contain other nutrients that protect against Parkinson\u2019s disease. More research is needed."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS):One large prospective study that followed nearly 1 million people for up to 16 years found that people who regularly took vitamin E supplements had a lower risk of dying from ALS than people who never took vitamin E supplements. [47] More recently, a combined analysis of multiple studies with more than 1 million participants found that the longer people used vitamin E supplements, the lower their risk of ALS. [48] Clinical trials of vitamin E supplements in people who already have ALS have generally failed to show any benefit, however. [49] This may be a situation where vitamin E is beneficial for prevention, rather than treatment, but more research is needed."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "There is no evidence of toxic effects from vitamin E found naturally in foods. Most adults who obtain more than the RDA of 22 IU daily are using multivitamins or separate vitamin E supplements that contain anywhere from 400-1000 IU daily. There have not been reports of harmful side effects of supplement use in healthy people. However, there is a risk of excess bleeding, particularly with doses greater than 1000 mg daily or if an individual is also using a blood thinning medication such as warfarin. For this reason, an upper limit for vitamin E has been set for adults 19 years and older of 1000 mg daily (1465 IU) of any form of tocopherol supplement. [1]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Researchers have tried to answer this question by combining the results of multiple studies. In one such analysis, the authors gathered and re-analyzed data from 19 clinical trials of vitamin E, including the GISSI and HOPE studies [50]; they found a higher rate of death in trials where patients took more than 400 IU of supplements a day. While this meta-analysis drew headlines when it was released, there are limitations to the conclusions that can be drawn from it. Some of the findings were based on very small studies. In some of these trials, vitamin E was combined with high doses of beta-carotene, which itself has been related to excess mortality.\u00a0 Furthermore, many of the high-dose vitamin E trials included in the analysis included people who had advanced heart disease or Alzheimer\u2019s disease. Other meta-analyses have come to different conclusions. So it is not clear that these findings would apply to healthy people. The Physicians\u2019 Health Study II, for example, did not find any difference in death rates between the study participants who took vitamin E and those who took a placebo. [13]"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Glynn RJ, Ridker PM, Goldhaber SZ, Zee RY, Buring JE. Effects of random allocation to vitamin E supplementation on the occurrence of venous thromboembolism: report from the Women\u2019s Health Study.Circulation. 2007;116:1497-503."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Another line of research about folate and two other B vitamins, vitamin B6 and vitamin B12, explores their roles in reducing some types of cancer and heart disease."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "When it comes toranking beverages best for our health, sugary drinks fall at the bottom of the list because they provide so many calories and virtually no other nutrients. People who drink sugary beverages do not feel as full as if they had eaten the same calories from solid food, and research indicates they also don\u2019t compensate for the high caloric content of these beverages by eating less food. [4] The average can of sugar-sweetened soda or fruit punch provides about 150 calories, almost all of them from added sugar. If you were to drink just one of these sugary drinks every day, and not cut back on calories elsewhere, you could gain up to 5 pounds in a year. Beyond weight gain, routinely drinking these sugar-loaded beverages can increase the risk of type 2 diabetes, heart disease, and other chronic diseases. Furthermore, higher consumption of sugary beverages has been linked with an increased risk of premature death. [5]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Agroundbreaking studyof 33,097 individuals showed that among people with a genetic predisposition for obesity, those who drank sugary drinks were more likely to have obesity than those who did not. [15] This study is important because it suggests that genetic risk for obesity does not need to become a reality if healthy habits, like avoiding sugary drinks, are followed. On the other hand, genetic obesity risk seems to be amplified by consuming sugary drinks.Read an interview with the study\u2019s lead researcher."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "A related study in women found a similar sugary beverage\u2013heart disease link. The Nurses\u2019 Health Study, which tracked the health of nearly 90,000 women over two decades, found that women who drank more than two servings of sugary beverage each day had a 40 percent higher risk of heart attacks or death from heart disease than women who rarely drank sugary beverages. [23]People who drink a lot of sugary drinks often tend to weigh more\u2014and eat less healthfully\u2014than people who don\u2019t drink sugary drinks, and the volunteers in the Nurses\u2019 Health Study were no exception. But researchers accounted for differences in diet quality, energy intake, and weight among the study volunteers. They found that having an otherwise healthy diet, or being at a healthy weight, only slightly diminished the risk associated with drinking sugary beverages.This suggests that weighing too much, or simply eating too many calories, may only partly explain the relationship between sugary drinks and heart disease. Some risk may also be attributed to the metabolic effects of fructose from the sugar or HFCS used to sweeten these beverages.The adverse effects of the high glycemic load from these beverages on blood glucose, cholesterol fractions, and inflammatory factors probably also contribute to the higher risk of heart disease. \u00a0Read more aboutblood sugar and glycemic load."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "People who drink a lot of sugary drinks often tend to weigh more\u2014and eat less healthfully\u2014than people who don\u2019t drink sugary drinks, and the volunteers in the Nurses\u2019 Health Study were no exception. But researchers accounted for differences in diet quality, energy intake, and weight among the study volunteers. They found that having an otherwise healthy diet, or being at a healthy weight, only slightly diminished the risk associated with drinking sugary beverages."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "A 22-year-long study of 80,000 women found that those who consumed a can a day of sugary drink had a 75% higher risk of gout than women who rarely had such drinks. [24] Researchers found a similarly-elevated risk in men. [25]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Results from a Women\u2019s Health Initiative study following 98,786 postmenopausal women (ages aged 50 to 79) for about 20 years found that participants who drank the highest amounts of sugar-sweetened beverages (SSB) had an increased risk of liver cancer. More specifically, those drinking 1 or more servings of SSB daily had an 85% higher risk of liver cancer than those who drank 3 or fewer servings of SSB per month. The participants used questionnaires to self-report their intakes of SSB (including soda and fruit drinks but not fruit juice) and diagnosis of liver cancer. The researchers also examined intakes of artificially sweetened beverages, comparing higher intakes of 1 or more servings per day with lower intakes of 3 or fewer servings per month, but did not find any association with liver cancer. [27]"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "After adjusting for major diet and lifestyle factors, the researchers found that the more sugary beverages a person drank, the more their risk of early death from any cause increased. Compared with drinking sugary beverages less than once per month, drinking one to four per month was linked with a 1% increased risk; two to six per week with a 6% increase; one to two per day with a 14% increase; and two or more per day with a 21% increase. The increased early death risk linked with sugary drink consumption was more apparent among women than among men."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The study also found that drinking one artificially sweetened beverage per day instead of a sugary one lowered the risk of premature death. However, drinking four or more artificially sweetened beverages per day was associated with increased risk of mortality in women, so researchers cautioned against excessive consumption ofartificially-sweetened beverages."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Results from a Women\u2019s Health Initiative study following 98,786 postmenopausal women (aged 50 to 79) for about 20 years found that participants who drank the highest amounts of sugar-sweetened beverages (SSB) had an increased risk of death from chronic liver diseases like nonalcoholic fatty liver disease, cirrhosis, chronic hepatitis, and fibrosis. [27] More specifically, those drinking 1 or more servings of SSB daily had a 68% higher risk of death from chronic liver disease than those who drank 3 or fewer servings of SSB a month. The participants used questionnaires to self-report their intakes of SSB (including soda and fruit drinks but not fruit juice) and diagnosis of chronic liver disease. The researchers also examined intakes of artificially sweetened beverages, comparing higher intakes of 1 or more servings per day with lower intakes of 3 or fewer servings per month, but did not find any association with deaths from chronic liver disease."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "A2019 analysis by the UConn Rudd Center for Food Policy and Obesityfound that kids ages 2-11 saw twice as many ads for sugary drinks than for other beverages, and they also saw four times as many ads for certain drinks than adults did. [41] Researchers also analyzed nearly 70 \u201cchildren\u2019s drinks\u201d (those marketed to parents and/or directly to children), and found that sweetened drinks contributed 62% of children\u2019s drink sales in 2018, including $1.2 billion in fruit drinks (90% of children\u2019s sweetened drink sales) and $146 million in flavored, sweetened water sales."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "National Cancer Institute. Sources of Calories from Added Sugars among the US population, 2005-2006. Risk Factor Monitoring and Methods Branch Web site. Applied Research Program. Mean intake of added sugars & percentage contribution of various foods among US population.http://riskfactor.cancer.gov/diet/foodsources/added_sugars/."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Coca-Cola Company.History of Bottling. Accessed June 2013:https://www.coca-colacompany.com/our-company/history-of-bottling"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "US Federal Trade Commission.Marketing Food to Children and Adolescents: A Review of Industry Expenditures, Activities, and Self-Regulation. Washington, DC: US Federal Trade Commission; 2008."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Avoid infant formulas from other countries unless they are approved by the FDA. FDA approvals are expected soon for formulas manufactured in Europe, for instance, so contact your health care provider (pediatrician, registered dietitian) with specific questions."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Steven A Abrams, Christopher P Duggan, Infant and child formula shortages: now is the time to prevent recurrences,\u00a0The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition, 2022;, nqac149,https://doi.org/10.1093/ajcn/nqac149.Author disclosures: SAA has received support from Abbott Nutrition related to presentations on nutritional physiology and from Perrigo Nutrition for research on food insecurity. CPD is the Editor-in-Chief of the AJCN."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Coffee lovers around the world who reach for their favorite morning brew probably aren\u2019t thinking about its health benefits or risks. And yet this beverage has been subject to a long history of debate. In 1991 coffee was included in a list of possible carcinogens by the World Health Organization. By 2016 it was exonerated, as research found that the beverage was not associated with an increased risk of cancer; on the contrary, there was a decreased risk of certain cancers among those who drink coffee regularly once smoking history was properly accounted for. Additional accumulating research suggests that when consumed in moderation, coffee can be considered ahealthy beverage. Why then in 2018 did one U.S. state pass legislation that coffee must bear a cancer warning label? Read on to explore the complexities of coffee."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Coffee is an intricate mixture of more than a thousand chemicals. [1] The cup of coffee you order from a coffee shop is likely different from the coffee you brew at home. What defines a cup is the type of coffee bean used, how it is roasted, the amount of grind, and how it is brewed. Human response to coffee orcaffeinecan also vary substantially across individuals. Low to moderate doses of caffeine (50\u2013300 mg) may cause increased alertness, energy, and ability to concentrate, while higher doses may have negative effects such as anxiety, restlessness, insomnia, and increased heart rate. [2] Still, the cumulative research on coffee points in the direction of a health benefit. [3,4] Does the benefit stem from the caffeine or plant compounds in the coffee bean? Is there a certain amount of coffee needed a day to produce a health benefit?"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "However, manycancer experts disputed the ruling, stating that the metabolism of acrylamide differs considerably in animals and humans, and the high amount of acrylamide used in animal research is not comparable to the amount present in food. They cited the beneficial health effects of coffee, with improved antioxidant responses and reduced inflammation, both factors important in cancer prevention. Evidence from the American Institute for Cancer Research concludes that drinking coffee mayreduce risk for endometrial and liver cancer, and based on a systematic review of a large body of research, it is not a risk\u00a0for the cancers that were studied."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "In June 2018, the California Office of Environmental Health Hazard Assessment (OEHHA) proposed anew regulationexempting coffee from displaying cancer warnings under Proposition 65. This proposal was based on a review of more than 1,000 studies published by the World Health Organization\u2019s International Agency for Research on Cancer that found inadequate evidence that drinking coffee causes cancer. In January 2019, OEHHA completed its review and response to comments and submitted the regulation to the Office of Administrative Law (OAL) for final review."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The bottom line:A large body of evidence suggests that consumption of caffeinated coffee does not increase the risk of cardiovascular diseases and cancers. In fact, consumption of 3 to 5 standard cups of coffee daily has been consistently associated with a reduced risk of several chronic diseases. [4] However, some individuals may not tolerate higher amounts of caffeine due to symptoms of jitteriness, anxiety, and insomnia. Specifically, those who have difficulty controlling their blood pressure may want to moderate their coffee intake. Pregnant women are also advised to aim for less than 200 mg of caffeine daily, the amount in 2 cups of coffee, because caffeine passes through the placenta into the fetus and has been associated with pregnancy loss and low birth weight. [3, 27] Because of the potential negative side effects some people experience when drinking caffeinated coffee, it is not necessary to start drinking it if you do not already or to increase the amount you currently drink, as there aremany other dietary strategiesto improve your health.Decaffeinated coffee is a good option if one is sensitive to caffeine, and according to the research summarized above, it offers similar health benefits as caffeinated coffee.It\u2019s also important to keep in mind how you enjoy your brew. The extra calories, sugar, and saturated fat in a coffee house beverage loaded with whipped cream and flavored syrup might offset any health benefits found in a basic black coffee."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "However, the real caloric danger occurs in specialty mochas, lattes, or blended ice coffee drinks. These drinks are often super-sized and can contain anywhere from 200-500 calories, as well as an extremely large amount of sugar. With these drinks, it\u2019s best to enjoy them as a treat or dessert, and stick with plain, minimally sweetened coffee on a regular basis"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Thank you for supporting our mission of translating food and nutrition knowledge into daily practice!Make a gift"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Although chickpea is a member of the \u2018founder crop package\u2019(Reference Zohary and Hopf15)with potential nutritional/medicinal qualities, it has not received due attention for research like other founder crops (e.g. wheat or barley). Chickpea has been consumed by humans since ancient times owing to its good nutritional properties. Furthermore, chickpea is of interest as a functional food with potential beneficial effects on human health. Although other publications have described the physico-chemical and nutritional characteristics of chickpea, there is limited information on the relationship between its nutritional components and health benefits. This review attempts to bridge this void and investigates the literature regarding the nutritional value of chickpeas and their potential health benefits."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "DF is the indigestible part of plant food in the human small intestine. It is composed of poly/oligosaccharides, lignin and other plant-based substances(39). DF can be classified into soluble and insoluble fibres. The soluble fibre is digested slowly in the colon, whereas the insoluble fibre is metabolically inert and aids in bowel movement(Reference Tosh and Yada40). The insoluble fibre undergoes fermentation aiding in the growth of colonic bacteria(Reference Tosh and Yada40). The total DF content (DFC) in chickpea is 18\u201322\u00a0g/100\u00a0g of raw chickpea seed(Reference Aguilera, Mart\u00edn-Cabrejas and Ben\u00edtez23,Reference Tosh and Yada40), and it has a higher amount of DF among pulses (Table 2). Soluble and insoluble DFC are about 4\u20138 and 10\u201318\u00a0g/100\u00a0g of raw chickpea seed, respectively(Reference Dalgetty and Baik29,Reference Rinc\u00f3n, Mart\u00ednez and Ib\u00e1\u00f1ez41). The fibre content of chickpea hulls on a dry weight basis is lower (75\u00a0%) compared with lentils (87\u00a0%) and peas (89\u00a0%)(Reference Dalgetty and Baik29). The lower DFC in chickpea hulls can be attributed to the difficulty in separating the hull from the cotyledon during milling."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "A fibre-rich chickpea-based pulse (non-soyabean) diet has been shown to reduce the total plasma cholesterol levels in obese subjects(Reference Crujeiras, Parra and Abete134). This study was conducted on thirty obese subjects (BMI 32\u00b70 (sd5\u00b73) kg/m2) with a mean age group of 36 (sd8) years. The subjects were divided into two groups of fifteen each and fed with a hypoenergetic diet consisting of a chickpea-based pulse diet and a control diet (no pulses) for a period of 8 weeks (4\u00a0d/week). After 8 weeks, the total cholesterol levels in the chickpea-based pulse diet-fed group decreased from 215 to 182\u00a0mg/dl, whereas a smaller decrease (181 to 173\u00a0mg/dl) was observed for the control diet-fed group(Reference Crujeiras, Parra and Abete134). The proposed mechanism for this hypocholesterolaemic effect is the inhibition of fatty acid synthesis in the liver by fibre fermentation products such as propionate, butyrate and acetate(Reference Crujeiras, Parra and Abete134). SCFA (e.g. propionate) have been shown to inhibit both cholesterol and fatty acid biosynthesis by inhibiting acetate (provides acetyl-CoA) utilisation(Reference Wright, Anderson and Bridges135). Feeding a chickpea diet to rats also resulted in a favourable plasma lipid profile(Reference Yang, Zhou and Gu136). In this study, thirty healthy male \u2018Sprague\u2013Dawley\u2019 rats were fed three different diets for 8 months: a normal-fat diet (5\u00a0g fat, 22\u00a0g protein and 1381\u00a0kJ/100\u00a0g); a high-fat diet (HFD; lard 20\u00a0% (w/w), sugar 4\u00a0% (w/w), milk powder 2\u00a0% (w/w) and cholesterol 1\u00a0% (w/w) into standard laboratory chow, which contained 25\u00b771\u00a0g fat, 19\u00b754\u00a0g protein and 1987\u00a0kJ/100\u00a0g diet); a HFD plus chickpea diet (same as the HFD, but 10\u00a0% crushed chickpea seeds replaced the standard chow; it contained 25\u00b711\u00a0g fat, 19\u00b736\u00a0g protein and 1965\u00a0kJ/100\u00a0g). Several pro-atherogenic factors, including TAG, LDL-C and LDL-C:HDL-cholesterol ratio, decreased with consuming the chickpea-based diet(Reference Yang, Zhou and Gu136). In eighty-four healthy \u2018Sprague\u2013Dawley\u2019 rats divided into fourteen groups of six each fed diets containing chickpea (49\u201365\u00b74\u00a0% of diet) and peas (46\u201362\u00a0% of diet) for 35\u00a0d, lower levels of plasma cholesterol were recorded(Reference Wang and McIntosh137). The decrease in cholesterol levels varied with the processing method used; extrusion and boiling had similar effects for chickpeas, whereas extrusion was most effective in peas. Phytosterols present in chickpea, along with other factors (e.g. isoflavones, oligosaccharides), reduce LDL-C levels in the blood by inhibiting the intestinal absorption of cholesterol due to the similarity in their chemical structure with cholesterol, thereby potentially reducing the risk of CHD(Reference Wood, Grusak, Yadav, Redden, Chen and Sharma9,Reference Pittaway, Ahuja and Robertson109)."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The information presented in this review shows the potential nutritional importance of chickpea and its role in improved nutrition and health. It is an affordable source of protein, carbohydrates, minerals and vitamins, DF, folate, \u03b2-carotene and health-promoting fatty acids. Scientific studies have provided some evidence to support the potential beneficial effects of chickpea components in lowering the risk of various chronic diseases, although information pertaining to the role of individual chickpea components in disease prevention and the mechanisms of action are limited to date. This is due to the complex nature of disease aetiology and various factors having an impact on their occurrence. It is imperative that the scientific community continues to unravel the mechanisms involved in disease prevention and determine how food bioactives from foods such as chickpea can influence human health. Further research, especially well-conducted RCT, needs to be performed to provide compelling evidence for the direct health benefits of chickpea consumption."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "We would like to acknowledge the ICRISAT library staff and other researchers for their help in this review. The authors have no conflict of interests to declare. A. K. J. acquired the necessary material and wrote most of the sections. P. M. G. and R. N. C. contributed to the writing of the nutritional aspects of the manuscript. P. M. G. also corresponded with the other authors. C. L. L. G. helped in writing the introduction part."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Please choose a valid location."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "To save this article to your Kindle, first ensure coreplatform@cambridge.org is added to your Approved Personal Document E-mail List under your Personal Document Settings on the Manage Your Content and Devices page of your Amazon account. Then enter the \u2018name\u2019 part of your Kindle email address below.Find out more about saving to your Kindle."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Your email address will be used in order to notify you when your comment has been reviewed by the moderator and in case the author(s) of the article or the moderator need to contact you directly."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/admissions-aid"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Our Southern California location allows our students to experience a land of innovation that is as forward looking as it is beautiful."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "We admit a first-year class representing a broad range of interests, viewpoints, talents and backgrounds. Guided by a need-blind admissions policy, financial need does not affect admissions decisions for U.S. citizens, permanent residents and/or for students graduating from a high school in the United States."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College is one of a handful of institutions committed to need-blind admissions and meeting the full demonstrated financial need of all students who enroll.56% of Pomona students receive some form of financial aid. The Need-Based Financial Aid commitment means a student's financial need is determined after a careful review of each family's financial documents. We do our best to take into account each family's unique circumstances."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/admissions/connect"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Webinars: Topics range from \u201cApplying to Pomona,\u201d to \u201cExploring Majors,\u201d and \u201cResearch & Internships.\u201d Q&A always included!"}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "From the Nest: Zoom chats with current students. Topics range from \"Student Clubs & Social Life\" to \"All About Academics\"."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Sagehen Stories: In this student-led blog, current Pomona College students share their experiences, insights, and advice on navigating life at the college."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "AdmissionsAdmissions A-ZWhy Pomona?ApplyConnect / VisitOn-Campus ProgramsVisit Pomona\u2014VirtuallyPomona Comes to YouPomona & Partner College EventsFor CounselorsFor FamiliesConnect with Your Admissions OfficerConnect with a StudentAdmitted StudentsDeferring EnrollmentWork / Volunteer for AdmissionsDiversity & AccessRequest Information"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Connect / VisitOn-Campus ProgramsVisit Pomona\u2014VirtuallyPomona Comes to YouPomona & Partner College EventsFor CounselorsFor FamiliesConnect with Your Admissions OfficerConnect with a StudentAdmitted StudentsDeferring EnrollmentWork / Volunteer for Admissions"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Connect with Your Admissions Officer"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Work / Volunteer for Admissions"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/admissions/diversity"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "At Pomona, diversity is crucial to our educational mission. Students enter with widely divergent backgrounds and experiences. Our 1,777 students come from all 50 states (as well as the District of Columbia, Guam, the Northern Mariana Islands and Puerto Rico) and more than 60 countries outside of the United States. Over half identify as domestic students of color and more than 18% are in the first generation of their family to attend a four-year college or university. Students at Pomona engage with, and learn from, peers, faculty, staff and community members whose identities and perspectives may differ considerably from\u2013and even challenge\u2013theirs. This complex intersection of identities and perspectives enriches the larger academic and social communities at Pomona"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Office of Admissions is deeply committed to admitting a class of individuals who bring a rich, broad set of experiences to the Pomona classroom and beyond. We understand that this is only possible if students from all backgrounds have access to connect/visit and apply with ease. It\u2019s why we offer intentional programs and policies such as:"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "You can submit aPomona Access Passif you plan to apply for financial aid and the application fee presents a hardship for you or your family."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Aneed-blind application reviewprocess in which financial need does not affect admissions decisions for U.S. citizens, permanent residents and/or for students graduating from a high school in the United States."}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Pomona College is one of a handful of institutions committed to meeting100% of demonstrated needof any admitted student eligible for need-based financial aid."}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "58% of students receive financial aid"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "A commitment to enrolling and supporting:undocumented studentssince 2007, through admissions and financial aid policies that remove barriers.veteransof the U.S. Armed Forces, exemplified by our membership in theYellow Ribbon Programand partnership withService to School's VetLink."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "undocumented studentssince 2007, through admissions and financial aid policies that remove barriers."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Academic Support Resourcesthat connect students with peers and professionals offering instruction in every discipline or coaching in general study or research skills."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Feel free to contactaccess@pomona.eduwith any questions."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "AdmissionsAdmissions A-ZWhy Pomona?ApplyConnect / VisitDiversity & AccessRequest Information"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Service to School has partnered with select colleges and universities to form VetLink, a network of schools committed to expanding access and opportunity for student veterans.\u00a0\u00a0Our partner colleges are widely known for academic excellence, aspiring students, leading-edge research, and high graduation rates."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Read MoreAside from Service to School\u2019s normal mentorship service, students are encouraged to use their VetLink program. Service to School VetLink applicants not only work one on one with a mentor, but they also work with a S2S staff member who guides them throughout the entire application process, and directly connects them with the admissions teams at their partner universities. This enables the student to better prepare their application, and each school receives supplemental information on the veteran student which highly increases the student\u2019s chance of being accepted."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Aside from Service to School\u2019s normal mentorship service, students are encouraged to use their VetLink program. Service to School VetLink applicants not only work one on one with a mentor, but they also work with a S2S staff member who guides them throughout the entire application process, and directly connects them with the admissions teams at their partner universities. This enables the student to better prepare their application, and each school receives supplemental information on the veteran student which highly increases the student\u2019s chance of being accepted."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Accomplishments (Faculty and Staff)"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty Employment Opportunities"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Institutional Research, Office of"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Summer research in Professor Karen Parfitt\u2019s lab"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Summer research with Professor Karen Parfitt"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Majors have the opportunity to assist faculty in research or conduct their own project through the Summer Undergraduate Research Program."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The major prepares students for a diverse array of career options, while giving students access to an extensive alumni network of scientists and researchers around the globe."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Neuroscience Department Faculty and Staff"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Undergraduate Research in Neuroscience"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Undergraduate Research in Neuroscience"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty for Undergraduate Neuroscience (FUN)"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/academics/departments/neuroscience/faculty-staff"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Neuroscience Department Faculty and Staff"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "ExpertiseExpertiseKarl Johnson\u2019s research is aimed at understanding how developing neurons find and make their appropriate synaptic connections in simple central nervous systems, usingDrosophila(the common fruit fly) as a model organism. His research focuses on identifying novel genes that are essential for two aspects of nervous system development\u2014first, how neurons find their proper synaptic targets, and second, how neurons build synapses.He and his team of undergraduate researchers have begun to characterize how heparan sulfate proteoglycans (HSPGs) influence central nervous system development, and are focusing their current efforts on examining the roles of two HSPGs, syndecan and dallylike, in axon guidance and synapse formation.Research InterestsJohnson\u2019s ongoing research is exploring the role a group of evolutionarily ancient molecules called heparin sulfate proteoglycans (HSPGs) play in central nervous system development in Drosophila.Areas of ExpertiseBiologyMolecular BiologyDevelopmental NeurobiologyDevelopmental BiologyAxon Guidance"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Karl Johnson\u2019s research is aimed at understanding how developing neurons find and make their appropriate synaptic connections in simple central nervous systems, usingDrosophila(the common fruit fly) as a model organism. His research focuses on identifying novel genes that are essential for two aspects of nervous system development\u2014first, how neurons find their proper synaptic targets, and second, how neurons build synapses."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "He and his team of undergraduate researchers have begun to characterize how heparan sulfate proteoglycans (HSPGs) influence central nervous system development, and are focusing their current efforts on examining the roles of two HSPGs, syndecan and dallylike, in axon guidance and synapse formation."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Johnson\u2019s ongoing research is exploring the role a group of evolutionarily ancient molecules called heparin sulfate proteoglycans (HSPGs) play in central nervous system development in Drosophila."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "WorkWorkWith D. Arizanovska and J. King. \u201cSyndecan affects odor response as well as learning and memory inDrosophila melanogaster.\u201dAmerican Journal of Undergraduate Research15(1): 23-32, 2018.With M. Nguyen, J., Kwong, J. Chang, V.G. Gillet, R.M. Lee. \u201cThe Extracellular and Cytoplasmic domains of Syndecan cooperate postsynaptically to promote synapse growth at theDrosophilaneuromuscular junction.\u201dPLOS One11(3):e0151621, 2016.With E. \u00d6zkan, R.A. Carrillo, C.L. Eastman, R. Weiszmann, D. Waghray, K. Zinn, S.E. Celniker, K.C. Garcia. \u201cAn Extracellular Interactome of Immunoglobulin and LRR Proteins Reveals Receptor-Ligand Networks.\u201dCell154(1):228-239, 2013.With I. Vilinsky. \u201cElectroretinograms inDrosophila: A robust and genetically accessible electrophysiological system for the undergraduate laboratory.\u201dJournal of Undergraduate Neuroscience Education11(1); A149-157, . 2012.With A.D. Smart, M.M. Course, J. Rawson, S. Selleck, D. Van Vactor. Heparan sulfate proteoglycan specificity during axon pathway formation in theDrosophilaembryo.Developmental Neurobiology71(7):608-618, 2011With A.P. Wright, A.N. Fox, and K. Zinn. \"Systematic screening ofDrosophiladeficiency mutations for embryonic phenotypes and orphan receptor ligands.PLoS ONE5(8): e12288, 2010With E. Stryker ('07), \"LAR, liprin-alpha and the regulation of active zone morphogenesis, \"Journal of Cell Science, 120: 3723-3728, 2007With A.P. Tenney, A. Duckworth, K. Parfitt, O. Marcu, T. Heslip, J. L. Marsh, J.G. Flanagan and D. Van Vactor, \"The HSPGs Syndecan and Dallylike bind the receptor phosphatase LAR and exert opposing effects on synapse growth,\"Neuron, 49(4): 517-531, 2006With D. Van Vactor and D.P. Wahl, \"Heparan Sulfate Proteoglycans and the emergence of neuronal connectivity, \"Curr. Op. Neurobiology, 16(1): 40-51, 2006With J.M. Rawson, B. Dimitroff, X. Ge, D. Van Vactor and S. B. Selleck, \"The heparan sulfate proteoglycans Dallylike and Syndecan have distinct functions in axon guidance and visual system assembly inDrosophila,\"Current Biology, Vol. 15:833-838, May 10, 2005With A. Ghose, E. Epstein, J. Lincecum, M. B. O'Connor and D. Van Vactor, \"Axonal heparan sulfate proteoglycans regulate the distribution and efficiency of the repellent Slit during midline axon guidance,\"Current Biology, 14:499-504, 2004"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "With D. Arizanovska and J. King. \u201cSyndecan affects odor response as well as learning and memory inDrosophila melanogaster.\u201dAmerican Journal of Undergraduate Research15(1): 23-32, 2018."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Awards & HonorsAwards & HonorsNational Science Foundation, Research at Undergraduate Institutions. Division of Integrative Organismal Systems \u2013 Neural Systems Cluster. \u201cInvestigating the mechanisms of Syndecan function during nervous system development\u201d $519,925 9/2009-8/2013National Institutes of Health, Academic Research Enhancement Award (AREA), three-year $216,556 grant for the project \"Characterizing the function of Syndecan during CNS [central nervous system] development,\" 2008 (Declined)Wig Distinguished Professorship Award for Excellence in Teaching, 2008 & 2014National Science Foundation and Davidson College, $10,000 SOMAS grant, designed to support the research of new neuroscience faculty and their students at predominantly undergraduate institutions, 2008Helen Hay Whitney Postdoctoral Fellow, 2002-2005Cambridge Overseas Research Studentship, 1997-2000Phi Beta Kappa, member, 1995-present"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "National Science Foundation, Research at Undergraduate Institutions. Division of Integrative Organismal Systems \u2013 Neural Systems Cluster. \u201cInvestigating the mechanisms of Syndecan function during nervous system development\u201d $519,925 9/2009-8/2013"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "National Institutes of Health, Academic Research Enhancement Award (AREA), three-year $216,556 grant for the project \"Characterizing the function of Syndecan during CNS [central nervous system] development,\" 2008 (Declined)"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "National Science Foundation and Davidson College, $10,000 SOMAS grant, designed to support the research of new neuroscience faculty and their students at predominantly undergraduate institutions, 2008"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Cambridge Overseas Research Studentship, 1997-2000"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Biology faculty believes strongly in the value of learning not just what is known about biology, but how biologists acquire that knowledge."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Biology faculty also encourages students to participate in biological research on campus. Located in the Richard C. Seaver Building, an innovative LEED-certified building, and the Seaver South Building, the Biology Department\u2019s facilities include controlled environment greenhouses\u00a0and laboratories equipped with advanced instrumentation."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "For field studies, the Claremont College\u2019s local Bernard Biological Field Station includes several natural habitats that serve research and courses in ecology, evolutionary biology, organismal biology, and animal behavior. The department also uses the Pomona College-owned Herman Garner Ecological Preserve in Claremont and the Mildred Pitt Ranch in Monterey County."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Gifts of any amount to theAnnual Fund,Family Fundor yourReunion Class Giftprovide immediate support for students by funding scholarships, academic departments and programs, and opportunities such as research, internships and community engagement."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "When engaging in stock transfers, pleasecontact Investments Officeso we can identify your gift when it arrives."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Our Annual Giving Associates student program, part of Student Philanthropy at Pomona College, creates an opportunity for students to get involved with philanthropic endeavors on behalf of Pomona. Through calling, email, texts and in-person events, Annual Giving Associates connect with alumni and families to share Pomona news and information, help to update contact information, advocate for and assist with giving back to Pomona and more. So, when your phone rings and you see (909) 607-4747 on the screen, be sure to answer with, \"Chirp!\" There is a Sagehen student on the other end who wants to talk with you!"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Can I use the IRA Qualified Charitable Distribution to support a particular purpose, like financial aid?"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "If you have questions about the tax implications of IRA Qualified Charitable Distributions,please contact us."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Participants in the Pomona Plan benefit from our long, accomplished history in managing life-income agreements. A pioneering institution in this area, Pomona issued its first charitable annuity in 1892 and developed the Pomona Plan in the 1940s. Today, it still sets the standard of planned giving programs among its peer institutions. This website provides information about the financial instruments offered under the Pomona Plan."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona CollegeMailing Address:The Pomona PlanAlexander Hall #238550 North College AvenueClaremont,CA91711(800) 761-9899"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "I\u2019ve seen how summer research allows students to gain command of an area in their chosen discipline, and carry the confidence and excitement from that experience forward in their undergraduate careers and beyond."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/faculty"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Use our faculty-specific A-Z for a list of pages curated just for faculty. You can also use our sitewide A-Z for general searches or the people search for directory listings."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Please use theFaculty A-Zto scan and search a list of links especially curated for faculty members at Pomona College."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty & Staff Accomplishments"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Contact the Office of Alumni & Family Engagement"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "I\u2019d like for the board to continue as a connecting force among the alumni community to strengthen and build relationships through opportunities like regional chapter events, career-focused programs, discussions with faculty and book club. And with the board on campus to help with Alumni Weekend each year, it\u2019s a unique moment for members to meet and talk with hundreds of alumni face-to-face, and with students. Part of my vision is growing the board\u2019s connection with the College from the perspective that students will be alumni longer than they will be students."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The generosity and collective foresight of alumni, faculty, staff, family and friends who have included Pomona in their estate plans help ensure that the College remains at the forefront of liberal arts education. \u00a0You can also impact future generations of Pomona students, faculty, and staff in this way by including a legacy gift for Pomona in your estate plan."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "I\u2019ve seen how summer research allows students to gain command of an area in their chosen discipline, and carry the confidence and excitement from that experience forward in their undergraduate careers and beyond."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College complies with all applicable state and federal civil rights laws prohibiting discrimination in education and the workplace. This policy of nondiscrimination covers admission, access and service in Pomona College programs and activities, as well as hiring, promotion, compensation, benefits and all other terms and conditions of employment at Pomona College."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "LiveSafeis a free personal safety mobile application for students, staff, faculty, and the community to engage in two-way conversation with Campus Safety."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The space above will be used to provide timely information for students, parents, faculty, staff, and other members of the College family. It will be updated regularly as new information becomes available."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "At all times, the College\u2019s highest priority is the safety and well-being of students, faculty and staff."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "The College is committed to getting accurate emergency alerts and information to members of the community as soon as possible. However, in the first minutes of an emergency, you may need to make an immediate decision to \u201cshelter in place\u201d or move to a safer location. You should understand and plan for both possibilities. Use common sense and available information, including what you are learning here, to determine if there is immediate danger."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Whether you are at home, work or elsewhere, there may be situations when it\u2019s best to stay where you are and avoid any rapidly changing or unknown situation outside. There are other circumstances when staying put and creating a barrier between yourself and potential danger is a matter of survival. Use available information to assess the situation."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Silence all electronics; set phones to vibrate."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "In either case, if there has been no emergency alert from the College or Campus Safety, please contact Campus Safety at (909) 607-2000 as soon as possible. They will send an alert to the community and provide information to the Pomona College Emergency Response Team."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Everbridge\u00a0Mass Notification is an emergency notification service that enables Campus Safety\u00a0to notify you quickly about a major emergency on campus and to provide you with information and instructions. Messages are sent via email, text and recorded message to campus phone extensions. Students, faculty and staff with a campus phone extension and college email\u00a0are already in the Everbridge\u00a0database. To add a cell phone number and/or home number, log on to the campus portal atmy.pomona.eduand click on the Everbridge\u00a0link. All contact information included in Everbridge will be used ONLY for campus emergency notification and will NOT be made available to any other service."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "LiveSafe is a free app that improves communication between students, faculty, staff and campus police and allows for faster emergency response in distress situations. By having access to the latest safety information, our goal is to help build a safe campus, together. The app allows students, faculty and staff to:"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Receive real-time safety alerts from campus police to your phone."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Visit the iTunes or Google Play store depending on your smartphone and download the \"LiveSafe\" app (blue shield icon)."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Fill in your emergency name and contact info so we can get in touch in the event of an emergency."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College has 49 emergency alert broadcast stations located throughout the campus that can be used as a public address system. In an emergency, they\u00a0will be used to broadcast warning tones and short messages. The stations with emergency phones, which are topped by blue lights, can also connect a user directly to Campus Safety when the red button is pushed."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "LiveSafe is a free personal safety mobile application for students, staff, faculty, and the community to engage in two-way conversation with Campus Safety."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "The College\u2019s highest priority is the safety and well-being of the community\u2019s students, faculty and staff. To this end, Pomona College has developed a comprehensiveEmergency Management Plan, regularly trains for various emergencies, and holds regular emergency and evacuation drills."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "You can help ensure that the College community is as prepared as possible by being familiar with the information on this website, making sure that your contact information (phone number and email) is up-to-date inEverbridgeand participating in all College emergency drills. You should also assemble a small personal \u201cgo bag,\u201d which could include extra glasses, contact lens solution, any necessary medication, and list of emergency family phone numbers."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "How to Update Your Emergency Contact Information"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "URL: https://locator.lacounty.gov/lac/Location/3178221/american-red-cross---claremont-chapter"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "\u201cI gave my first gift to Pomona as a first-year. Working as a caller for the Annual Fund, I knew participation was key to the success of the program. I also give because of the generous financial aid I receive.\u201d"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "For further information about Pomona College, you may find contact information and websites for our offices and departmentsin the Pomona College directory."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Claremont Colleges\u2019 phone operator may be reached at (909) 621-8000. Mail may be sent to the appropriate office at the following address:"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College complies with all applicable state and federal civil rights laws prohibiting discrimination in education and the workplace. This policy of nondiscrimination covers admission, access and service in Pomona College programs and activities, as well as hiring, promotion, compensation, benefits and all other terms and conditions of employment at Pomona College."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College is accredited by the Accrediting Commission for Senior Colleges and Universities of the Western Association of Schools and Colleges (985 Atlantic Ave., Suite 100, Alameda, CA 94501; 510-748-9001). WASC is an institutional accrediting body recognized by the Council on Postsecondary Accreditation and the U.S. Department of Education."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Offices, Campus Locations and Organizations"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "It directs a number of curricular and other programs designed to promote the teaching and learning of foreign languages and international studies: the Language Resident program, conversation courses for academic credit, daily language tables, luncheon colloquia, the Foreign Language Resource Center (FLRC), summer research and travel grants, and the Exchange Visitor Program (J visa). Students, staff, and faculty from\u00a0across The Claremont Colleges engage with these programs."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "It directs a number of curricular and other programs designed to promote the teaching and learning of foreign languages and international studies: the Language Resident program, conversation courses for academic credit, daily language tables, luncheon colloquia, the Foreign Language Resource Center (FLRC), summer research and travel grants, and the Exchange Visitor Program (J visa). Students, staff, and faculty from\u00a0across The Claremont Colleges engage with these programs."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Yidan Endowed Fund offers summer support for the study of Asia. The Oldenborg Travel Grants offer financial support for international research for a senior thesis."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Please see section below for faculty and staff, and community members."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "When and where do language tables take place?"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "All students, faculty, and staff must enter through the dining hall main door and then proceed to find their language table signaled with the appropriate sign."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Where can I find the language table schedule?"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Can faculty and staff participate in language tables?"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Oldenborg encourages 7C faculty and staff to participate in language tables! Whether it\u2019s for improving your own language skills or offering expertise in a language you are fluent in, we hope that you join us."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Do faculty and staff need to pay for a meal when attending language tables?"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Oldenborg welcomes faculty and staff\u2019s active participation at language tables and is pleased to cover the cost of their lunch meal."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Faculty and/or staff who have meal swipes available are welcome to utilize this at Oldenborg."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Admission is at Oldenborg\u2019s discretion and there is a $10 charge per visit."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "I was born in Beijing, the capital of China, where there are lots of places of interest like the Great Wall and the Forbidden City. It is a charming place not only because it integrates traditional and modern culture but also because people from all over the world gather here, creating an open and welcoming atmosphere. Living in this international and dynamic city helps me have more chances to make friends and have insight into diverse cultures. I really love this city and welcome all of you to come to Beijing in the future!"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Frary is Pomona's largest dining hall, located on north campus. Frary features a main entr\u00e9e line, exhibition station, vegan/vegetarian section, soups, pizza and grill stations, sandwich, salad and dessert bars, as well as a full selection of beverages. Frary is open for breakfast, lunch and dinner during the week and brunch and dinner on the weekends and holidays.\u00a0 Students, faculty and staff from all of The Claremont Colleges frequent Frary's grand dining room, watched over Jose\u00e9 Clemente's famous Prometheus painting. Frary also has two private dining rooms."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Oldenborg dining hall offers exciting international cuisine at its entr\u00e9e lines and specialty salad, soup, and dessert stations. Luncheon guests can also find more familiar fare at the pizza station and salad and sandwich bars. Students, staff, and faculty from across the 7Cs enjoy daily foreign language tables and also attend lectures from distinguished visitors on a host of international topics. These two co-curricular academic programs are mainstays of the Oldenborg Center for Modern Languages and International Relations, a jewel of the Pomona campus and a rite of passage for many language students and international visitors. Oldenborg offers a private dining room, conference room, and television lounge, all of which can be reserved for luncheon meetings. Oldenborg dining hall is open for lunch each day that classes are in session on the Pomona campus. Learn more information aboutOldenborg Center programming."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/administration/dining/contact"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "We are committed to nurturing an engaged, thriving, safe and healthy community that is responsive to student needs. The Dean of Students Office is committed to providing equal access and reasonable accommodations, where appropriate, for qualified disabled students. The College will continue to develop and coordinate policies and procedures, provide services, and insure access to academic programs, activities and facilities."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Accessibility Resources and Services Mission Statement"}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "We envision a diverse and accessible campus community that is responsive to the needs of students with disabilities. The ARS Office will continue to develop policies and procedures, provide services, and programming that ensure equal access and opportunity to all aspects of campus life."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Equity means seeking full participation and thriving for everyone by recognizing that people do not all start from the same place and working to intentionally address barriers and power imbalances."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Inclusion means respecting the humanity of all people by striving to create an environment where people feel like they belong and are accepted as they are, inclusive of all identities they hold."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Our compliance with federal and state law is a shared responsibility in which faculty play an important role. This page provides information and resources to assist you in creating an accessible learning environment."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Student AccessibilityStudent ResourcesDocumentation GuidelinesTypes of DisabilitiesTypes of AccommodationsAccommodation Policies and ProceduresFaculty CornerDisability Grievance ProcedureRequest Accessibility Ally TrainingOur Staff"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "If a student is denied their requested accommodation that they believe is necessary, the student may take their concerns to theDean of Students for Academic and Personal Success.\u00a0Students should fill out the \"Accommodation Reconsideration Form\" and include additional information that supports their request. Students may attach additional documentation that addresses the reasons given by ARS for the denial. The Dean will evaluate the matter and make appropriate recommendations within five (5) working days of receiving the additional information.\u00a0If an agreement cannot be reached, the Senior Associate Dean of Students can review the original request."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Dr. Adaly Reyes Martinez serves as the college's Director of Accessibility.\u00a0 She is located in the Dean of Students Office, Pomona College, 550 N. College Ave, Claremont, CA, 91711. Contact information: disability@pomona.edu 909-621-8017."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Student AccessibilityStudent ResourcesDocumentation GuidelinesTypes of DisabilitiesTypes of AccommodationsAccommodation Policies and ProceduresFaculty CornerDisability Grievance ProcedureRequest Accessibility Ally TrainingOur Staff"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "\u201cI gave my first gift to Pomona as a first-year. Working as a caller for the Annual Fund, I knew participation was key to the success of the program. I also give because of the generous financial aid I receive.\u201d"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "For further information about Pomona College, you may find contact information and websites for our offices and departmentsin the Pomona College directory."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Claremont Colleges\u2019 phone operator may be reached at (909) 621-8000. Mail may be sent to the appropriate office at the following address:"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College complies with all applicable state and federal civil rights laws prohibiting discrimination in education and the workplace. This policy of nondiscrimination covers admission, access and service in Pomona College programs and activities, as well as hiring, promotion, compensation, benefits and all other terms and conditions of employment at Pomona College."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College is accredited by the Accrediting Commission for Senior Colleges and Universities of the Western Association of Schools and Colleges (985 Atlantic Ave., Suite 100, Alameda, CA 94501; 510-748-9001). WASC is an institutional accrediting body recognized by the Council on Postsecondary Accreditation and the U.S. Department of Education."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "We welcome new students for information sessions, advising and team-building activities, where you'll learn what it means to be a member of the Pomona community."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Read up on these to get a jump start on life as a Pomona student."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Academic Life: This includes\u00a0placement exams, Breadth of Study (general ed) requirements for graduation, and how to register for classes. Your faculty advisor will also assist you with this process."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "New Student GuideAcademic LifeComputers & AccountsStudent Employment"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Links will go live throughout the Spring and Summer of 2024 and include deadlines and contact information. Links are only live when the form/website is available."}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "If you wish to complete your enrollment, make your enrollment deposit, and view your financial aid information, visit the Destination Pomona portal."}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Financial Aid Account Review(login through Pomona Portal)"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Photo ID Submission Form(due date:July 21)"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Emergency Contact Information Form(due date:August 10)"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "The Tuition Payment Agreement Form is now available. You received an email with a DocuSign form and the subject line in your Pomona inbox is \u201cURGENT \u2013 Mandatory 2024-25 Tuition Payment Agreement.\u201d If you have questions, contactstudent.accounts@pomona.edu. All students are required to complete and sign this form every year. It is due on June 28."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Higher EdOverviewResidence LifeCareer ServicesStudent Conduct"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Contact UsGet SupportTalk to Us"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Symplicity establishes systems and operational requirements that support the achievement of service commitments, relevant laws and regulations, and other security and privacy requirements.Privacy Policies are important because they detail a company\u2019s views and procedures regarding the information collected fromusers.Symplicity takes ourprivacy policies and procedures obligations seriously.Symplicityis the global leader inhigher education student services applications.Leading the way among EdTech companies, we\u2019ve worked with outside privacy counsels all over the world to ensure compliance withmultiple data privacy frameworksin the regionswherewe supporthigher educationinstitutionssuch as the GDPR/UK-GDPR, PIPEDA,CCPA,The Privacy Act, LGPD,PDPA, and more."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Symplicity's Data Protection Officer (DPO) is the main point of contact for the data protection authority, responsible for overseeing the company's data protection strategy and its implementation to ensure compliance with GDPR requirements."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "We have a multi-layered\u202fapproach to data transfer compliance. This means we address data transfer requirements via multiple avenues to ensure personal information is adequately protected:"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Symplicity has a regional hosting strategy.\u00a0 That means that your data will be stored in the data zone where the application was licensed.\u00a0 For example, if you licensed your application in the United States, your data will ONLY be stored in the United States."}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "U.S. Colleges Game Out a Possible End to Race-Conscious Student Admissions"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "To learn more about the numbers and facts behind Pomona College and its students and faculty -- including student body size, number of majors, and faculty/student ratio -- visit ourFast Facts\u00a0page."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College, located in Claremont, California, is one of the nation's premier liberal arts colleges. Established in 1887, it is the founding member of The Claremont Colleges, and is known for small classes, a challenging curriculum, close relationships between students and faculty, and a range of student research and leadership opportunities."}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "The College is a leading producer of Fulbright scholars and recipients of other competitive fellowships and scholarships.\u00a0Committed to college access, Pomona is one of a handful of colleges that meet the full financial aid need of every accepted student with scholarships."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College faculty includes accomplished scholars in the liberal arts and sciences in topics of national and international scope that range from immigration policies and higher education to international diplomacy and nuclear weapons. Many have shared their expertise with national and international media, and are available for interviews on current events."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "For media requests with Pomona College professors, please contactpatricia.vest@pomona.eduormarilyn.thomsen@pomona.edu."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Pomona College, one of the nation\u2019s liberal arts colleges, is the founding member of The Claremont Colleges in Southern California. Pomona College is known for its range of quality academic programs, interdisciplinary studies, opportunities for student research, close relationships between faculty and students."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "To reach our faculty experts, contact Marilyn Thomsen atmarilyn.thomsen@pomona.eduor (909) 838-4578. You can also view acomplete list of Pomona College faculty."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "ExpertiseExpertiseColin J. Beck is a political sociologist interested in a classic big question of sociology\u2014how and why do societies and institutions change? He primarily examines this question through the lens of revolution, as revolutions are times when alternative social orders are imagined, authored and potentially enacted. In particular, his award-winning work on revolutionary waves draws on global-transnational sociology to understand why multiple revolutions occur simultaneously and how they affect each other.An interest in revolution almost necessarily leads to its contemporary counterparts\u2014terrorism and social movement radicalism.\u00a0As one of the few sociological experts on multiple forms of political violence, he has examined cases as diverse as radical environmental activism, political Islam, 18th century Enlightenment revolutions, and the Arab Spring.Beck is the author ofRadicals, Revolutionaries, and Terrorists(2015), a book based on a seminar of the same name that he has taught at Pomona since 2010. He is a member of the International Relations Program in addition to the Department of Sociology, and has held elected positions in the American Sociological Association.Research InterestsRevolutionary wavesRadical social movements and terrorismComparative methodsAreas of ExpertiseSOCIOLOGYPolitical sociologySocial movementsComparative and historical sociologyGlobal and transnational sociologyPOLITICSGlobalizationRevolutionTerrorism and political violence"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "WorkWorkBooksRadicals, Revolutionaries, and Terrorists(Polity Press; 2015)Articles\u201cThe Structure of Comparison in the Study of Revolution,\u201dSociological Theory36(2):134-161, 2018\u201cThe Comparative Method in Practice: Case Selection and the Social Science of Revolution,\u201dSocial Science History43(3):533-554, 2017\"Reflections on the Revolutionary Wave in 2011,\"Theory and Society43(2):197-223, 2014With E. Miner (PO '12), \"Who Gets Designated a Terrorist and Why?\"Social Forces91(3):837-872, 2013With G.S. Drori and J.W. Meyer, \"World Influences on Human Rights Language in Constitutions: A Cross-National Study,\"International Sociology27(4):483-501, 2012\"The World Cultural Origins of Revolutionary Waves: Five Centuries of European Contention,\"Social Science History35(2):167-207, 2011\"State-Building as a Source of Islamic Political Organization,\"Sociological Forum24(2):337-356, 2009\u201cOn the Radical Cusp: Ecoterrorism in the United States, 1998-2005,\u201dMobilization12(2):161-176, 2007"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "\u201cThe Comparative Method in Practice: Case Selection and the Social Science of Revolution,\u201dSocial Science History43(3):533-554, 2017"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "\"The World Cultural Origins of Revolutionary Waves: Five Centuries of European Contention,\"Social Science History35(2):167-207, 2011"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "EducationEducation2009, Ph.D., SociologyStanford University2002, Master of Arts, SociologyStanford University2000, Bachelor of ArtsLewis & Clark CollegeRecent Courses TaughtGlobal Systems and SocietyHistory & Development of Sociological Theory I: The Classical TraditionIntroduction to SociologyRadicals, Revolutionaries, and TerroristsSocial and Political MovementsSurvey and Quantitative Research Methods"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "History & Development of Sociological Theory I: The Classical Tradition"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Survey and Quantitative Research Methods"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Social movements, revolutions, and terrorism share similar causes and processes. In my first book, I consider eight key questions for understanding radicalism. Ranging across the globe from the 1500s to the present, diverse cases are examined, e.g., 19th century anarchists, fascists, Che Guevara, the Weather Underground, Chechen insurgents, the Earth Liberation Front, Al-Qaeda, and the Arab Spring. Throughout, I demonstrate how to draw on multiple areas of research to better explain the forms movements take. The book is based on a seminar of the same name I have taught since 2010."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "My primary area of expertise is revolutions. In my work on revolutionary waves, I find that cultural constructions of the transnational system strain regimes, fracture elites, and empower oppositions as well as make cross-national diffusion more likely. Articles published inTheory and SocietyandSocial Science Historyhave won awards from sections of the American Sociological Association."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Comparative Method in Practice: Case Selection and the Social Science of Revolution,Social Science History2017"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The World-Cultural Origins of Revolutionary Waves,Social Science History2011"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Revolution's contemporary counterparts include radicalism, political violence, and terrorism. I use insights from sociology and social movement theory to explain different aspects of political violence. Currently, I am extending my research on terrorism designations to understand media labeling of militant groups."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The international human rights regime is the mirror image of radicalism and political violence in the contemporary world. My research explores the dynamics of the international system and domestic politics. Kristen Shorette, John Meyer, Gili Drori, and I currently are investigating human rights in national constitutions."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "I am a professor atPomona Collegein Claremont, California, and a faculty affiliate of theInternational Relations Program."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "My research lies in the areas of political and global-transnational sociology with quantitative and comparative-historical approaches. I am particularly interested in revolutions. This almost necessarily leads to an interest in revolution's contemporary counterparts\u2014radicalism and terrorism\u2014and their mirror image in international human rights."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "At Pomona, I teach courses on social movements, global sociology, research methods, and social theory."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Address:140 W. 6th St., Claremont, CA 91711, USA"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.smith.edu/academics/faculty/mlada-bukovansky"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Discover SmithExpand Discover Smith MenuSmith in ActionHistory & TraditionsPresident Sarah Willie-LeBretonVisit the CampusGovernanceSmith at a GlanceContact Smith"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "AcademicsExpand Academics MenuPrograms & CoursesOur Approach To LearningIntegrative LearningFaculty DirectoryAcademic CalendarRegistrarClass DeansProvost/Dean of the FacultyStudy AbroadLibraries"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Admission & AidExpand Admission & Aid MenuApply to SmithVisits & ProgramsLife After Smith: Career OutcomesTuition & Aid for ApplicantsAid for Current StudentsFor Parents & FamiliesFor School & CBO Counselors"}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Your CampusExpand Your Campus MenuHealth & WellnessResidence LifeDining & MenusCommunityOffices & ServicesClubs & OrganizationsStudent Government AssociationAthleticsFor New StudentsSmithArts"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Mlada Bukovansky\u2019s research focuses on the evolving norms and institutions of the international system. She has written on revolutions and changing conceptions of sovereignty, corruption and anti-corruption regimes, the World Trade Organization and agricultural trade, and U.S. responsibilities in a changing world order. Her current work focuses on international ethics and on the challenges to the liberal international order. She has a longstanding interest in the intersection between the study of history, especially the history of political thought, and that of international relations."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Mlada Bukovansky, Edward Keene, Christian Reus-Smit, and Maja Spanu, eds.,The Oxford Handbook of History and International Relations(Oxford University Press, forthcoming 2023)"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Discover SmithExpand Discover Smith MenuSmith in ActionHistory & TraditionsPresident Sarah Willie-LeBretonVisit the CampusGovernanceSmith at a GlanceContact Smith"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "AcademicsExpand Academics MenuPrograms & CoursesOur Approach To LearningIntegrative LearningFaculty DirectoryAcademic CalendarRegistrarClass DeansProvost/Dean of the FacultyStudy AbroadLibraries"}, {"question": "What are the admission requirements at Pomona College?", "answer": "Admission & AidExpand Admission & Aid MenuApply to SmithVisits & ProgramsLife After Smith: Career OutcomesTuition & Aid for ApplicantsAid for Current StudentsFor Parents & FamiliesFor School & CBO Counselors"}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "Your CampusExpand Your Campus MenuHealth & WellnessResidence LifeDining & MenusCommunityOffices & ServicesClubs & OrganizationsStudent Government AssociationAthleticsFor New StudentsSmithArts"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Smith College does not have a single office or administrator that responds to all consumer information questions. If you have questions about a particular federal disclosure requirement or other specific consumer information, please visit the subject link below. The administrator title and contact information will be included on the linked page or pages. Administrators are available to answer questions, upon reasonable notice, during the normal working hours of the college."}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Financial Aid Code of Conductfor educational loans"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Types of financial aid, including Direct Loans"}, {"question": "What financial aid options does Pomona College offer?", "answer": "Requirements for withdrawal and refunds of financial aid"}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "Smith College employs freelance and staff photographers to take photos and video of students, classes, activities and the campus for promotional, marketing and archival purposes. Members of the Smith community acknowledge that they may appear in photography and videos taken for these purposes.\u00a0The college reserves the right to use, publish, display and reproduce these photos and video in various college materials, including theSmith College website, brochures, social media and other outlets. For more information on this policy, contact the Office of College Relations, 413-585-2180."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "When class size averages 15 and the student faculty ratio is 8:1, bonds are bound to be tight. Pomona offers access to some of the best professors in the world."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Learning at Pomona often happens outside the classroom through hands-on experiences in research, internships and community engagement."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Courses at any of the 5Cs are open to you and advanced students may, with permission, enroll in master\u2019s level courses in their area of specialization at Claremont Graduate University."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "During a semester abroad in Morocco, Haley Kirtland \u201924 conducted ethnographic research on how water rituals in rural Morocco were deeply intertwined with agricultural irrigation practices."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Among our Religious Studies faculty members are professors awarded for their excellence in teaching. We have experts on a range of topics, including gender and sexuality studies and the Bible, corporate polytheism, modern Jewish philosophy, women and Islam, and Chinese Buddhist art."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "gain strong familiarity with at least one religious tradition, be able to recognize its manifestations in text and in culture, and be able to engage in informed discussion of its beliefs, history, and practice, as well as of issues and questions that accrue to its study."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "carry out sustained research on a topic that integrates classroom exposure with original investigation."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/academics/departments/religious-studies/undergraduate-research-religious-studies"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Undergraduate Research in Religious Studies"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "At Pomona College, students from all disciplines are encouraged to undertake research. Some apply for funded focused summer research through theSummer Undergraduate Research Program. Below are recent projects completed by students in the Religious Studies Department."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Despite the traditional US educational model that seeks to explain genocide solely through the events of the Holocaust, the field of Genocide Studies, which emerged in the direct aftermath of WWII, can in fact be reframed to form a nuanced deconstruction of Holocaust discourse that helps to establish a new understanding of the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. I used my SURP grant, provided through my partnership with the Pomona College Humanities Studio, to jumpstart my senior thesis research by constructing a method to apply the extensive Holocaust discourse accessible today to the multiplicity of perspective on the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. I did this by conducting extensive archival research in Washington DC with the United States Holocaust Memorial Museum and other organizations, gathering interview and other hands-on data from sources in Palestine, Israel, and Germany, synthesizing research sources I acquired in my time studying in both the Czech Republic and Morocco, and working with the NGO Genocide Watch to explore their model of historical and contemporary genocidal processes. This work has led me to conclude that unlike any other historical event, the Holocaust can uniquely be used not only to provide invaluable insight into the Israeli and Jewish diaspora identity and perspective on the conflict, but also to establish a framework for understanding genocide that sheds light on the Palestinian narrative and crimes being perpetrated against them."}, {"question": "What is student life like at Pomona College?", "answer": "\u201cRaised in the Pews: The Second-Generation Chinese American Christian Experience in the South\u201d was a study on Chinese American Christians who have grown up in the Southern United States. The goal was to find how cultural differences with older generations and their peers influence the religious experience and perspectives of Chinese Americans from the South with both older generations and their peers. The study was done using quota sampling of Chinese Americans from two Chinese churches in the South who had grown up there. Participants were each interviewed to give insight on how they feel their ethnic background influences the role that Christianity plays in their life and their identity. The study showed that second-generation Chinese American Christians who are brought up in the South see common ethnic background contributing to how they can build communities in church. Many described the desire to share a common ethnic background with those who they go to church with and the impact that it has. Individuals also expressed that a common faith acted as a bridge with peers of different ethnicities, often even emphasizing shared faith above ethnic difference.\u00a0 Some also expressed the influence of differences between themselves and older generations within church. The study begins to provide a perspective on the religious experience of second-generation Chinese American Christians raised in the South and the impacts of cultural and generational difference.Funding Provided By: Aubrey H & Eileen J Seed Student Research Fund"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "The Department of Religious Studies stands firmly with the call issued by the Intercollegiate Department of Africana Studies in pledging \u201cto root out the scourge of anti-Blackness wherever it is discovered and however it manifests in the culture a"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "When I initially came to Pomona, I barely knew what religious studies was. I took a wide range of courses my first year, embracing what it means to be \u201cundeclared.\u201d The more time I spent exploring various fields though, the more my interests broadened. During the fall of my second year, I took my first two religious studies courses: Eye of God: Race and Empire and Religion and American Politics. In my Religion and American Politics course, I studied the relevance of religion in U.S. history and policy, focusing my term research on reproductive rights. Eye of God had a multi-media approach that challenged me to analyze and question texts unlike I ever had before. I was surprised by how different these courses were, and I quickly became hooked on the intellectual opportunities in the religious studies field. While my concentration is in religion and politics, I have taken courses ranging from Children\u2019s Literature to God on Trial: Free Will and Evil."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "One of my favorite things about the religious studies major is how I have been able to combine my environmental interests with religious studies topics and theories. As a double major with environmental analysis, I have always been curious about human relationalities to the environment. My religious studies major has given me tools to conduct research and ask belief-based questions, solidifying my interest in the intersection of the two. During my semester abroad in Morocco, I focused my independent study on community water politics. In this ethnographic research, I explored how water rituals in rural Morocco were deeply intertwined with agricultural irrigation practices. This year, I have had the opportunity to do thesis research on similar topics in religion and the environment with the support of my professors and the department."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "I have always had a passion for studying the history of different cultures, and in 7th grade history class, I remember learning about Islam for the first time. From that point on, I fell in love with the study of religion. I came to Pomona College planning to major in religious studies and have only been more certain of my decision the more courses I have taken in the field. There are so many great aspects of the major, one of which is the broadness of study. My fellow religious studies majors have so many diverse research areas that you would hardly believe they are in the same major. My area of concentration is Christian studies, and my research area is Medieval Christianity, with a focus in female saints' lives. This ties in nicely with my minor\u2013late antique medieval studies."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "The Religious Studies Department allows me to explore that intersection of religious studies, history, and gender and women's studies, and encourages that interdisciplinary approach. I even participated in a 2023 Summer Undergraduate Research Project at Pomona on hymnology related to Saint Brigit of Kildare, a female late antique medieval Irish saint. Within the flexibility of the department, my major advisor, Professor Kenneth Wolf, is in the adjacent department of Classics. Since his courses and research areas are religion-focused and align well with my interests, I am able to work well with him on my academic journey. Another aspect of the major's interdisciplinary nature is that courses outside of the department that are related to it can count toward your major. In my case, I took \"Music in Christian Practice\" with Professor YouYoung Kang at Scripps College, and this was one of my favorite courses I have taken in college. In looking at the intersection between music and Christianity, I was able to count the course toward my major and learned about topics that inspired my summer research project."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Personal, identifying information about you is collected and stored only when you provide it voluntarily\u2014for example, when you fill out and submit a web form, send us an email expressly containing such information, or participate in SagehenConnect. This information is used to provide you with more targeted information about the College or its programs and to enable connections for Pomona alumni, students, staff, faculty, and families, as well as to enhance the user experience and services provided through SagehenConnect. The College takes every reasonable precaution to keep such information secure. It is never shared with any other organization, except as required by law or in those cases in which we have engaged an outside organization to provide services on behalf of the College. In the latter case, the outside organization is required to keep such information confidential and prohibited from using it for any other purpose."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "At various points in our web, we provide links to other servers that may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for and exercise no control over the views or accuracy of the information contained on these outside websites. Also, if you wish to make a text link from your website to any portion of ours, you may do so without asking permission."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "If you have any other questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact us at:webmaster@pomona.edu."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Talk title: TBAAmbassador Dennis Ross and Ghaith al-OmariWednesday, November 20Time: TBARose Hills Theatre, Smith Campus CenterPomona CollegeIntercollegiate Religious Studies Pre-Registration EventTime & Location: TBA"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "The Department of Religious Studies stands firmly with the call issued by the Intercollegiate Department of Africana Studies in pledging \u201cto root out the scourge of anti-Blackness wherever it is discovered and however it manifests in the culture and operations of the Colleges.\u201d"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Religious Studies offers\u00a0a cooperative major/minor jointly with Claremont McKenna, Harvey Mudd, Pitzer and Scripps colleges. Courses at any of the 5Cs are open to you and advanced students may, with permission, enroll in master\u2019s level courses in their area of specialization at Claremont Graduate University."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/academics/departments/religious-studies/faculty-staff"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Religious Studies Faculty and Staff"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Religious Studies Emeriti Faculty"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "ExpertiseExpertiseZayn Kassam is the John Knox McLean Professor of Religious Studies at Pomona College, Claremont, California. A graduate of McGill University (Ph.D. 1995), she teaches courses on mysticism, gender, literature, ethics, and the environment.She has lectured widely on gender issues in the United States, Canada, and Britain. She has been honored with three Wig Awards for Distinguished Teaching at Pomona College, as well as an American Academy of Religion Excellence in Teaching Award.\u200bKassam is the author ofIntroduction to the World's Major Religions: Islam(2006), and editor ofWomen and Islam(2010) andWomen in Asian Religions(2018). She is also the section editor for Islam for the volume on Islam, Judaism, and Zoroastrianism for theEncyclopedia of Indian Religions(2018).She\u00a0has chaired\u00a0the department of religious studies at Pomona College, and has coordinated the programs in gender and women\u2019s studies, Asian studies\u00a0and\u00a0Middle Eastern studies.\u00a0She is currently\u00a0the director of the Pacific Basin Institute. She serves on several national editorial boards, including theJournal of Feminist Studies in Religionand theJournal of the American Academy of Religion.Research InterestsMuslim MigrationAreas of ExpertiseGender and IslamIslamic Philosophy and MysticismReligion and the Environment"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "WorkWork\u201cCaught in the Crosshairs: Muslims and Migration.\u201d Ch. 7 inReligion, Protest, and Social Upheaval, edited by Matthew T. Eggemeier, Peter Joseph Fritz, and Karen V. Guth, Fordham University Press, 2021.\u201cMuslimah Theology and Praxis.\u201d Ch. 14 inHandbook on Women\u2019s Studies in Religion, edited by Helen Boursier, Rowman & Littlefield, 2021.\u201cMernissi, Fatima.\u201d Entry for Encyclopedia of Islam, Third Edition, 2021.\u201cMuslims and Migration:\u00a0 Global Realities, Local Opportunities.\u201d Chapter inWhere are we? Pastoral Environments and Care for Migrants, edited by Daniel Schipani, Martin Walton, Dominiek Lootens, Society for Intercultural Pastoral Care and Counselling, D\u00fcsseldorf, Germany, 2017.\u201cMuslim Liberative Approaches and Legal Dilemmas Towards Gender Justice.\u201d Chapter inThe Bible and Feminism: Remapping the Field,.\u201d (Edited by Yvonne Sherwood. Oxford University Press, 2017).\u201cChild Soldiers and the Militarization of Children:\u00a0 A Muslim Ethical Response to the Situation in the Sudan.\u201d Chapter inThe Bloomsbury Reader in Religion and Childhood. \u00a0(Edited by Anna Strhan, Stephen Parker, and Susan Ridgely.\u00a0 Bloomsbury Press, 2017).\u201cMuslims in America:\u00a0The Challenges of Migration and the Construction of Religious Identities.\u201d Chapter inIntersections of Religion and Migration: Issues at the Global Crossroads. (Edited by Jennifer B. Saunders, Elena Fiddian-Qasmiyeh, and Susanna Snyder.\u00a0 Under contract with Palgrave MacMillan, 2017).\u201cGender.\u201d\u00a0Substantively revised entry forThe Encyclopedia of Islam and the Muslim World. (2nd edition, 2016).With Bridget Blomfield, \u201cRemembering F\u0101\u1e6dimah and Zaynab:\u00a0 Gender in Perspective.\u201d Chapter inThe Shi\u2019a World.\u00a0 (Edited by Amyn Sajoo, Farhad Daftary, and Shainool Jiwa.\u00a0 Muslim Heritage Series, I.B. Tauris for The Institute of Ismaili Studies. UK, 2015).\u201cReligious Studies and Hermeneutics.\u201d\u00a0 Entry forEncyclopedia of Women and Islamic Cultures. (Ed. Suad Joseph. Brill.\u00a02014).\u201cIslam and Food.\u201d Entry forThe Encyclopedia of Food. (Entry jointly authored with Sarah Robinson.\u00a0 Springer Press 2014).\u201cSeptember 11, 2001, and Islam.\u201d Ch. 44 in Scott S. Elliott, ed.,Reinventing Religious Studies:\u00a0 Key Writings in the History of a Discipline.\u00a0 (UK, Acumen Publishing 2014).\u201cDignity and Relationality: A Conversation with Zayn Kassam.\u201d Chapter inSpeaking of the Qur\u2019an. (Edited by Michael Berkel. Baylor University Press, 2014).\u201cRe-Reading the Qur\u2019\u0101n from a Gender Perspective.\u201d Chapter inFeminist Biblical Studies in the 20thCentury.(Elisabeth Sch\u00fcssler-Fiorenza, ed., Society of Biblical Literature Press, 2014).\u201cTheologies and Ethics of Migration: Muslim and Christian Perspectives.\u201d Co-authored with Susanna Snyder, Anna Rowlands, and Narzanin Massoumeh. Chapter inRescripting Religion in the City: Migration and Religious Identity in the Modern Metropolis.\u00a0(Alana Harris and Jane Garnett, eds., Ashgate Press, 2013).\u201cConstructive Interreligious Dialogue Concerning Muslim Women.\u201d Chapter inWomen and Interreligious Dialogue. (Catherine Cornille, ed., Boston University Press, 2013).\u201cIslam, Gender, and Peace.\u201d Chapter inTerrorism, Religion, and Global Peace: From Conception to Praxis.(K. Kuriakose, ed., Gorgias Press, 2012).\u201cWhom Shall I Kill?\u201d Chapter inEncountering the Stranger: A Jewish, Christian, Muslim Trialogue. (John Roth and Leonard Grob, eds., University of Washington Press, 2012).\u201cNecrophilia and Voyaging: Some Curious Connections.\u201d Special Issue Celebrating and Cerebrating Mary Daly (1928\u20132010).Journal of Feminist Studies in Religion,28:2, 2012.\u201cThe Challenges of Globalization for Muslim Women.\u201d Chapter inThe Oxford Handbook of Feminist Theology.(Mary McClintock Ferguson and Sheila Briggs, eds., Oxford: Oxford University Press, 2011).\u201cThe Gender Policies of Aga Khan III and Aga Khan IV.\u201d Chapter 5 inA Modern History of the Ismailis. (Farhad Daftary, ed., I.B. Tauris and The Institute of Ismaili Studies, 2011).Other WorkIslam, Judaism, and Zoroastrianism. Islam Section Editor (Springer, 2018).Women and Asian Religions. Editor.\u00a0 Women and Religion in the World Series.\u00a0(Santa Barbara, CA: Praeger ABC-CLIO, 2017).Editor,Women and Islam(Praeger, 2010)Introduction to the World's Major Religions: Islam(Greenwood Press, December 2006)."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "\u201cMuslims and Migration:\u00a0 Global Realities, Local Opportunities.\u201d Chapter inWhere are we? Pastoral Environments and Care for Migrants, edited by Daniel Schipani, Martin Walton, Dominiek Lootens, Society for Intercultural Pastoral Care and Counselling, D\u00fcsseldorf, Germany, 2017."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "\u201cSeptember 11, 2001, and Islam.\u201d Ch. 44 in Scott S. Elliott, ed.,Reinventing Religious Studies:\u00a0 Key Writings in the History of a Discipline.\u00a0 (UK, Acumen Publishing 2014)."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "\u201cThe Gender Policies of Aga Khan III and Aga Khan IV.\u201d Chapter 5 inA Modern History of the Ismailis. (Farhad Daftary, ed., I.B. Tauris and The Institute of Ismaili Studies, 2011)."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "EducationEducationPh.D., History of Religions, 1995, McGill UniversityM.A., Islamic Studies, 1985, McGill UniversityB.A., Religious Studies, 1977, McGill UniversityRecent Courses TaughtCritical Inquiry SeminarDivine Body: Rel and EnvironmentEngendering and Experience: Women in the Islamic TraditionReligion, Ethics, and Social Practice"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Ph.D., History of Religions, 1995, McGill University"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "ExpertiseResearch InterestsChinese Buddhist history and artBuddhist cults with a special focus on Dizang (Jizo) BodhisattvaBuddhist cross-cultural interactionsInterface between texts and imagesTaiwanese Buddhist modernityAreas of ExpertiseRELIGIONBuddhist StudiesChinese Religion"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Chinese Buddhist history and art"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "WorkWork\u201cFrom Bodily Relic to Dharma Relic Stupa: Chinese Materialization of the Asoka Legend in Tenth-century Southeast China,\u201d inIndia in the Chinese Imagination, edited by John Kieschnick and Meir Shahar (University of Pennsylvania Press, 2013).\"The Architectural and Religious Functions ofBaoqieyin Dharani-sutraManuscripts at Leifeng Pagoda in Tenth-Century Hangzhou,\" with a Japanese translation by Yamano Chieko, in Strategic Research Project of Japanese Manuscripts of Buddhist Scriptures and the International College for Postgraduate Buddhist Studies, eds.,Manuscripts in the Kongo-ji Collection: The Bao qie yin tuoluoni jing, Bibliotheca Codicologica Nipponica VI(Tokyo:, 2013).\"Contextualizing Buddhist Approaches to Religious Diversity: When and How Buddhist Intellectuals Address Confucianism and Daoism (3rd\u20139th c.),\" inReligious Diversity in Chinese Thought, edited by Perry Schmidt-Leukel and Joachim Gentz (Palgrave, 2013).\"Scriptural Authority: A Buddhist Perspective,\"Buddhist-Christian Studies30: 85-105, 2010\"Buddhist Responses to State Control of Religion in China at the Century's Turn,\" inBuddhist Approaches to Human Rights: Dissonances and Resonances, edited by Carmen Meinert and Hans-Bernd Z\u00f6llner (Transcript-verlag, 2010)The Making of a Savior Bodhisattva: Dizang in Medieval China. Kuroda Institute Studies in East Asian Buddhism Series no. 21. Published in cooperation with University of Hawai'i, 2007\"The Maitreya Connection in Tang Development of Dizang Worship,\"Harvard Journal of Asiatic Studies65.1, 99-132, 2005"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "\"The Architectural and Religious Functions ofBaoqieyin Dharani-sutraManuscripts at Leifeng Pagoda in Tenth-Century Hangzhou,\" with a Japanese translation by Yamano Chieko, in Strategic Research Project of Japanese Manuscripts of Buddhist Scriptures and the International College for Postgraduate Buddhist Studies, eds.,Manuscripts in the Kongo-ji Collection: The Bao qie yin tuoluoni jing, Bibliotheca Codicologica Nipponica VI(Tokyo:, 2013)."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "\"Contextualizing Buddhist Approaches to Religious Diversity: When and How Buddhist Intellectuals Address Confucianism and Daoism (3rd\u20139th c.),\" inReligious Diversity in Chinese Thought, edited by Perry Schmidt-Leukel and Joachim Gentz (Palgrave, 2013)."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "EducationEducationPh.D.University of ArizonaMaster of ArtsUniversity of Michigan, Ann ArborBachelor of ArtsNational University of SingaporeRecent Courses TaughtLife-Story of the Buddha: Art, Ritual, Text & FilmReligious Traditions of ChinaReligious Traditions of JapanThe Lotus Sutra in East Asia: A History of the BookThe World of Mahayana Scriptures: Art, Doctrine, & PracticeTradition or Innovation? The Making of Modern Chinese BuddhismWorlds of Buddhism"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "The Lotus Sutra in East Asia: A History of the Book"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Awards & HonorsAwards & HonorsUniversity of Heidelberg: Visiting Research Fellow, Material Textual Culture Project and Stone Buddhist Texts Project, 2012OWBA Foundation, Bangkok: Outstanding Women in Buddhism Award, 2010National University of Singapore; Asia Research Institute Visiting Senior Research Fellow, 2009\u201310Chiang Ching-kuo Foundation; Scholar Grant, 2008\u201309Graves Award for Excellence in Teaching, 2004-05Harvard University; Center for the Study of World Religions Senior Fellow, 2003-04The University of Arizona; Dean's Fellow Award, 1998"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "University of Heidelberg: Visiting Research Fellow, Material Textual Culture Project and Stone Buddhist Texts Project, 2012"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "National University of Singapore; Asia Research Institute Visiting Senior Research Fellow, 2009\u201310"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "ExpertiseExpertiseDarryl Smith specializes in philosophy of religion, African American letters and theology and American pragmatism. He is also a faculty member of The Claremont Colleges Intercollegiate Department of Africana Studies.Research InterestsThe Art of Living and Informed SustainabilityAfrican Diasporic ThoughtSignification as Spiritual PracticePragmatism and Natural PietyDeath and Dying in Ancient AfricaAreas of ExpertiseRELIGIONPhilosophy of ReligionAfrican American Letters and TheologyAmerican PragmatismTheodicy and the Problem of EvilAfrofuturismDeathways in Ancient Egypt and Nubia"}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Darryl Smith specializes in philosophy of religion, African American letters and theology and American pragmatism. He is also a faculty member of The Claremont Colleges Intercollegiate Department of Africana Studies."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "WorkWork\u201cHandi-/Cappin\u2019 Slaves and Laughter by the Dozens: Divine Dismemberment and Disability Humor in the U.S.\u201dJournal of Literary and Cultural Disability Studies, Vol. 7, No. 3, University of Liverpool. October 2013.\u201cSouls/Soles of Signs: Tell Totems and the Sphinx Wager,\u201d inFrontiers in Chance: Gaming Research Across the Disciplines, David G. Schwartz, ed. UNLV Gaming Press. Las Vegas. 2013.\u201cScions of Cyclops: Race, Millennial Optics, and the American Cult of the Sun,\u201d inMis/Representing Evil: Evil in an Interdisciplinary Key, Charlene P. E. Burns, ed. Interdisciplinary Press. Oxford, England. 2009.\u201cDroppin\u2019 Science Fiction: Signification and Singularity in the Metapocalypse of Du Bois, Baraka, and Bell,\u201dScience Fiction Studies, Vol. 34, Part 2, DePauw University. July 2007: 201-219.\u201cThe Pretended,\u201dDark Matter: A Century of Speculative Fiction from the African Diaspora, Sher\u00e9e R. Thomas, ed., Warner Books, New York. 2000."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "\u201cSouls/Soles of Signs: Tell Totems and the Sphinx Wager,\u201d inFrontiers in Chance: Gaming Research Across the Disciplines, David G. Schwartz, ed. UNLV Gaming Press. Las Vegas. 2013."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "EducationEducationPh.D., Princeton UniversityM.A., Princeton UniversityM.Phil., University of CambridgeM.Div., Harvard UniversityB.A.,\u00a0University of Nevada, RenoRecent Courses TaughtCritical Inquiry SeminarIndependent Research in Religious StudiesInterpreting Religious WorldsThe Art of LivingThe Holy Fool: The Comic, the Ugly, and Divine MadnessThe Problem of Evil: African-American Engagements with(in) Western Thought"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Independent Research in Religious Studies"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "ExpertiseExpertiseErin Runions\u2019s research focuses on the Hebrew Bible and its reception history, with special attention to the influence of the Bible on contemporary culture and politics. In her work, she demonstrates the cumulative effect of biblical reception on sexuality, biopolitics, racialization, governance, war, torture and U.S. imperialism. Her publications include, The Babylon Complex: Theopolitical Fantasies of War, Sex, and Sovereignty (2014); How Hysterical: Identification and Resistance in the Bible and Film (2003); Changing Subjects: Gender, Nation, Future in Micah (2001).Runions has also been an activist for many years, working on issues of police brutality and prison injustice, globalization, antiwar activism, feminist and queer organizing. She currently helps facilitate a writing workshop inside a women\u2019s prison and is working on issues of environmental justice in the nearby city of Pomona.Research InterestsThe intersections of biblical interpretation and political philosophies, with their multiple impacts on political subjectivity, gender, sexuality, U.S. national sovereignty, and biopoliticsAreas of ExpertiseRELIGIONHebrew BibleCultural StudiesGender and Sexuality Studies and the BibleBible and Film; Religion and FilmApocalypse and MillenniumBible and PoliticsPHILOSOPHYPoststructuralism"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Erin Runions\u2019s research focuses on the Hebrew Bible and its reception history, with special attention to the influence of the Bible on contemporary culture and politics. In her work, she demonstrates the cumulative effect of biblical reception on sexuality, biopolitics, racialization, governance, war, torture and U.S. imperialism. Her publications include, The Babylon Complex: Theopolitical Fantasies of War, Sex, and Sovereignty (2014); How Hysterical: Identification and Resistance in the Bible and Film (2003); Changing Subjects: Gender, Nation, Future in Micah (2001)."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "WorkWork\u201cImmobile Theologies, Carceral Affects: Interest and Debt in Faith-Based Prison Programs.\u201dAffectivity and Divinity: Affect Theories and Theologies, ed. Karen Bray and Stephen A. Moore, 55-84. New York: Fordham University Press, 2020.\u201cSexual Politics and Surveillance: A Feminist, Metonymic, Spinozan Reading of Psalm 139.\u201d InThe Bible and Feminism: Remapping the Field, ed. Yvonne Sherwood, 296-314. Oxford: Oxford University Press, 2017.\u201cThe Bible as Biopolitics inObergefell v. Hodges: Theopolitical Subtexts and the Economic Management of Democracy.\u201dPolitical Theology17.5 (2016): 465-85.Review essay, \u201cGehenna Trauma, Prison Hell.\u201d A review essay ofThe Lives of Objects: Material Culture, Experience, and the Real in the History of Early Christianityby Maia Kotrosits.Religious Studies Review47.3 (2021): 307-309.Review essay, \u201cDivine Currencyand Carceral Sacrificonomics in the Time of COVID-19.\u201d A review essay ofDivine Currency: The Theological Power of Money in the West, by Devin Singh.Critical Research on Religion9.1 (2021): 98-102.The Babylon Complex: Theopolitical Fantasies of War, Sex and Sovereignty(Fordham University Press, 2014)."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "Review essay, \u201cGehenna Trauma, Prison Hell.\u201d A review essay ofThe Lives of Objects: Material Culture, Experience, and the Real in the History of Early Christianityby Maia Kotrosits.Religious Studies Review47.3 (2021): 307-309."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Review essay, \u201cDivine Currencyand Carceral Sacrificonomics in the Time of COVID-19.\u201d A review essay ofDivine Currency: The Theological Power of Money in the West, by Devin Singh.Critical Research on Religion9.1 (2021): 98-102."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Awards & HonorsAwards & HonorsLilly Endowment, Wabash Center Grant for workshops for university and college faculty on pedagogies for civic engagement in the study of religion, 2008-2009 [with Reid Locklin, Forrest Clingerman, and Clark Chilson].Lilly Endowment, Wabash Center, summer research stipend, 2007.Lilly Endowment, Wabash Center Grant for participation in the Workshop on Teaching and Learning for Pre-Tenure Religion Faculty at Colleges and Universities, 2006-2007.Fonds pour la formation de chercheurs et l'aide \u00e0 la recherche, Qu\u00e9bec; Postdoctoral Fellowship held at Barnard College, 2000-02; Doctoral Fellowship, 1995-96."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Lilly Endowment, Wabash Center Grant for workshops for university and college faculty on pedagogies for civic engagement in the study of religion, 2008-2009 [with Reid Locklin, Forrest Clingerman, and Clark Chilson]."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Lilly Endowment, Wabash Center, summer research stipend, 2007."}, {"question": "What is the student-to-faculty ratio at Pomona College?", "answer": "Lilly Endowment, Wabash Center Grant for participation in the Workshop on Teaching and Learning for Pre-Tenure Religion Faculty at Colleges and Universities, 2006-2007."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "at Pomona College. Her research focuses on the Hebrew Bible and its reception"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "history, with special attention to the influence of Christian interpretation on"}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "This timely book analyzes the resurgent influence of the Bible since 9.11, tracking the surprisingly frequent and contradictory political allusions to\u00a0 Babylon in U.S. politics and culture. References to Babylon reveal much about the way biblical logics (often secularized) mediate a conflicted sense of political and financial control in times of uncertain global markets. Shaped by philosophy, culture, political discourse, and the history of biblical reception, the apocalyptic figure of Babylon becomes the writing on the wall for national fears and ambitions. Babylon reflects, depicts, and shapes national imaginaries around the war in Iraq, torture, family values, sexuality, democracy, citizenship, tyranny, freedom, the market, and the shape of national sovereignty."}, {"question": "What is the history of Pomona College?", "answer": "This timely book analyzes the resurgent influence of the Bible since 9.11, tracking the surprisingly frequent and contradictory political allusions to\u00a0 Babylon in U.S. politics and culture. References to Babylon reveal much about the way biblical logics (often secularized) mediate a conflicted sense of political and financial control in times of uncertain global markets. Shaped by philosophy, culture, political discourse, and the history of biblical reception, the apocalyptic figure of Babylon becomes the writing on the wall for national fears and ambitions. Babylon reflects, depicts, and shapes national imaginaries around the war in Iraq, torture, family values, sexuality, democracy, citizenship, tyranny, freedom, the market, and the shape of national sovereignty."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "We want to make Threads the place where people, especially creators and businesses, connect with new and existing audiences around their interests and experiences. In June, we launched the Threads API to enable developers to build their own unique integrations, and help creators and brands manage their Threads presence at scale, easily sharing..."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Earlier this year, we announced theAI Sandboxwhere we\u2019ve been testing these generative AI features with a small and diverse set of advertisers. These advertisers have been providing us with valuable feedback, including helping us ensure these products arebuilt responsibly. Here's what they've said about Meta\u2019s generative AI for ads:"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Select your audience.You can build an audience based on age, gender, location and interests. To start, think of your typical customers and try to replicate that audience here."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Decide where to run your ad.You can run your ads on Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, Audience Network or across them all. We recommend Advantage+ placements, which allows Meta to serve your ads where they\u2019ll do best."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Select your audience.You can build an audience based on age, gender, location and interests. To start, think of your typical customers and try to replicate that audience here."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Decide where to run your ad.You can run your ads on Facebook, Instagram, Messenger, Audience Network or across them all. We recommend Advantage+ placements, which allows Meta to serve your ads where they\u2019ll do best."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Select your placements. These include numerous placements on Facebook and Instagram, including Stories, Reels, Feed and more. You can also select Advantage+ placements, which allows Meta to select the placements where the system predicts your ads will do best."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Select your placements. These include numerous placements on Facebook and Instagram, including Stories, Reels, Feed and more. You can also select Advantage+ placements, which allows Meta to select the placements where the system predicts your ads will do best."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Provide your email address to receive the latest updates from Meta for Business, including news, events and product updates."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Security research into the adversarial networks we\u2019ve taken down since 2017"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Additional tools for in-depth research on Meta technologies and programs"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Meta recognizes how important it is for Facebook to be a place where people feel empowered to communicate, and we take our role seriously in keeping abuse off the service. That\u2019s why we developed standards for what is and isn\u2019t allowed on Facebook."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Other research tools and datasets"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Security research into the adversarial networks we\u2019ve taken down since 2017"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Additional tools for in-depth research on Meta technologies and programs"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Media outlets reported an incident of alleged police brutality during the ongoing transport protests in Colombia. The outlets often shared a video where a slur can incidentally be heard in the background, therefore violating our Hate Speech policy. We issued a newsworthy allowance for this video given its public interest value, which outweighed the risk of harm from hearing the incidental use of a slur. However, given that the video also included graphic content, we placed a warning screen over this content and limited its availability to adults ages 18 and older."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "The video was posted to a page depicting men in military uniforms being beaten and mocked by a group of men wearing different military uniforms. The caption claimed the perpetrators were Azerbaijani soldiers. Under our Coordinating Harm and Promoting Crime policy on outing, Meta removes content revealing the identity of prisoners of war in the context of an armed conflict, where exposure of identity can present a risk of offline harm. However, with no evidence videos like this being used in the conflict to further mistreat the detainees and there being trends of similar content available through other sources, the safety risks were not high. On the other hand, the videos were raising awareness about the conditions of the prisoners and potential violations of international humanitarian law against them and are highly relevant to campaigns and legal proceedings for accountability of serious crimes. Ultimately the video was allowed, with a warning screen, as a newsworthy decision after weighing the risk of safety and dignity of prisoners of war against the public interest value of sharing this imagery. The Oversight Board issued a decision upholding Meta\u2019s decision to leave up the content."}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "Other research tools and datasets"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/researchtools/meta-content-library/"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/researchtools/ad-library-tools"}, {"question": "What research opportunities are available at Pomona College?", "answer": "URL: https://www.pomona.edu/researchtools/other-datasets/"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Not share your password, give access to your Facebook account to others, or transfer your account to anyone else (without our permission)."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "We've previously disabled your account for violations of our Terms or theCommunity Standards, or other terms and policies that apply to your use of Facebook. If we disable your account for a violation of our Terms, the Community Standards, or other terms and policies, you agree not to create another account without our permission. Receiving permission to create a new account is provided at our sole discretion, and does not mean or imply that the disciplinary action was wrong or without cause."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "You may not access or collect data from our Products using automated means (without our prior permission) or attempt to access data you do not have permission to access."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Permission to use content you create and share:Some content that you share or upload, such as photos or videos, may be protected by intellectual property laws.You retain ownership of the intellectual property rights (things like copyright or trademarks) in any such content that you create and share on Facebook and otherMeta Company Productsyou use. Nothing in these Terms takes away the rights you have to your own content. You are free to share your content with anyone else, wherever you want.However, to provide our services we need you to give us some legal permissions (known as a \"license\") to use this content. This is solely for the purposes of providing and improving our Products and services as described in Section 1 above.Specifically, when you share, post, or upload content that is covered by intellectual property rights on or in connection with our Products, you grant us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, and worldwide license to host, use, distribute, modify, run, copy, publicly perform or display, translate, and create derivative works of your content (consistent with yourprivacyandapplicationsettings). This means, for example, that if you share a photo on Facebook, you give us permission to store, copy, and share it with others (again, consistent with your settings) such as Meta Products or service providers that support those products and services. This license will end when your content is deleted from our systems.You can delete individual content you share, post, and upload at any time. In addition, all content posted to your personal account will be deleted if you delete your account.Learn moreabout how to delete your account. Account deletion does not automatically delete content that you post as an admin of a page or content that you create collectively with other users, such as photos in Shared Albums which may continue to be visible to other album members.It may take up to 90 days to delete content after we begin the account deletion process or receive a content deletion request. If you send content to trash, the deletion process will automatically begin in 30 days unless you chose to delete the content sooner. While the deletion process for such content is being undertaken, the content is no longer visible to other users. After the content is deleted, it may take us up to another 90 days to remove it from backups and disaster recovery systems.Content will not be deleted within 90 days of the account deletion or content deletion process beginning in the following situations:where your content has been used by others in accordance with this license and they have not deleted it (in which case this license will continue to apply until that content is deleted);where deletion within 90 days is not possible due to technical limitations of our systems, in which case, we will complete the deletion as soon as technically feasible; orwhere immediate deletion would restrict our ability to:investigate or identify illegal activity or violations of our terms and policies (for example, to identify or investigate misuse of our Products or systems);protect the safety, integrity, and security of our Products, systems, services, our employees, and users, and to defend ourselves;comply with legal obligations for the preservation of evidence, including data Meta Companies providing financial products and services preserve to comply with any record keeping obligations required by law; orcomply with a request of a judicial or administrative authority, law enforcement or a government agency;"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "where your content has been used by others in accordance with this license and they have not deleted it (in which case this license will continue to apply until that content is deleted);"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "where deletion within 90 days is not possible due to technical limitations of our systems, in which case, we will complete the deletion as soon as technically feasible; or"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "where immediate deletion would restrict our ability to:investigate or identify illegal activity or violations of our terms and policies (for example, to identify or investigate misuse of our Products or systems);protect the safety, integrity, and security of our Products, systems, services, our employees, and users, and to defend ourselves;comply with legal obligations for the preservation of evidence, including data Meta Companies providing financial products and services preserve to comply with any record keeping obligations required by law; orcomply with a request of a judicial or administrative authority, law enforcement or a government agency;"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Permission to use your name, profile picture, and information about your actions with ads and sponsored or commercial content:You give us permission to use your name and profile picture and information about actions you have taken on Facebook next to or in connection with ads, offers, and other sponsored or commercial content that we display across our Products, without any compensation to you. For example, we may show your friends that you are interested in an advertised event or have liked a Facebook Page created by a brand that has paid us to display its ads on Facebook. Ads and content like this can be seen only by people who have your permission to see the actions you've taken on Meta Products. You canlearn moreabout your ad settings and preferences."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Permission to update software you use or download:If you download or use our software, you give us permission to download and install updates to the software where available."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "You may designate a person (called a legacy contact) to manage your account if it is memorialized. If you enable it in your settings, only your legacy contact or a person who you have identified in a valid will or similar legal document expressing clear consent to disclose your content to that person upon death or incapacity will be able to seek limiteddisclosureof information from your account after it is memorialized."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "c. Protecting the Rights of Othersi. You will not provide or promote content in your App that infringes upon or otherwise violates the rights of any person or third party.ii. You will obtain (and represent and warrant that you own or have secured) all rights necessary from all applicable rights holders to (1) grant the licenses, rights, and permissions in these Terms (including those in Section 2.b (\u201cYour License to Us\u201d)); (2) display, distribute, and deliver all information, data, and other content in your App; and (3) otherwise operate your App. This includes satisfying all licensing, reporting, and payout obligations to third parties.iii. If your App contains content submitted or provided by your Users or other third parties, you must have an appropriate notice and takedown process and otherwise comply with all applicable laws and regulations to respond to notices of claimed infringement.  Without limiting that compliance, in the United States, you must comply with all requirements of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "ii. You will obtain (and represent and warrant that you own or have secured) all rights necessary from all applicable rights holders to (1) grant the licenses, rights, and permissions in these Terms (including those in Section 2.b (\u201cYour License to Us\u201d)); (2) display, distribute, and deliver all information, data, and other content in your App; and (3) otherwise operate your App. This includes satisfying all licensing, reporting, and payout obligations to third parties."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "c. Sharing Platform Data.You may only share Platform Data in compliance with these Terms (including Sections 3.a (\u201cProhibited Practices\u201d), 3.b (\u201cAdditional Terms for Restricted Platform Data\u201d), 4 (\u201cPrivacy Policy\u201d), and 5 (\u201cService Providers and Tech Providers\u201d)), applicable law and regulations, and all other applicable terms and policies, and only in the following circumstances:i. With respect to Platform Data collected as a Tech Provider, solely as described below in Section 5.b (\u201cTech Providers\u201d);ii. With respect to Platform Data not collected as a Tech Provider,1. when required under applicable law or regulation (you must retain proof of the applicable legal or regulatory requirement or request and provide it to us if we ask for it);2. with your Service Provider;3. when a User expressly directs you to share the data with a third party (you must retain proof of the User\u2019s express direction and provide it to us if we ask for it); or4. solely with respect to Platform Data that is not Restricted Platform Data, with other third parties, so long as:a. you first contractually prohibit them from using the Platform Data in a way that would violate these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies (you must retain proof of the contractual prohibition and provide it to us if we ask for it); andb. you ensure that any such third parties comply with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies as if they were in your place, and you are responsible for their acts and omissions, including their noncompliance."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "ii. With respect to Platform Data not collected as a Tech Provider,1. when required under applicable law or regulation (you must retain proof of the applicable legal or regulatory requirement or request and provide it to us if we ask for it);2. with your Service Provider;3. when a User expressly directs you to share the data with a third party (you must retain proof of the User\u2019s express direction and provide it to us if we ask for it); or4. solely with respect to Platform Data that is not Restricted Platform Data, with other third parties, so long as:a. you first contractually prohibit them from using the Platform Data in a way that would violate these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies (you must retain proof of the contractual prohibition and provide it to us if we ask for it); andb. you ensure that any such third parties comply with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies as if they were in your place, and you are responsible for their acts and omissions, including their noncompliance."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "4. solely with respect to Platform Data that is not Restricted Platform Data, with other third parties, so long as:a. you first contractually prohibit them from using the Platform Data in a way that would violate these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies (you must retain proof of the contractual prohibition and provide it to us if we ask for it); andb. you ensure that any such third parties comply with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies as if they were in your place, and you are responsible for their acts and omissions, including their noncompliance."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "b. you ensure that any such third parties comply with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies as if they were in your place, and you are responsible for their acts and omissions, including their noncompliance."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "a. Service Providersi. You will not use a Service Provider in connection with your use of Platform or Processing of Platform Data unless such Service Provider first agrees in writing to do the following:1. Use Platform and Process Platform Data solely for you and at your direction in order to provide services you requested in a manner that is consistent with these Terms, all other applicable terms and policies, and your privacy policy, and for no other individual or entity and for no other purpose, including for the Service Provider\u2019s own purposes; and2. In the event the Service Provider engages another Service Provider (\u201cSub-Service Provider\u201d) in order to provide the services requested, ensure the Service Provider requires the Sub-Service Provider in writing to comply with the above requirements.ii. You must ensure that any Service Provider and Sub-Service Provider complies with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies as if they were in your place, and you are responsible for their acts and omissions, including their noncompliance.iii. When you cease using a Service Provider or Sub-Service Provider, you must ensure they immediately cease using Platform and Processing Platform Data and promptly delete all Platform Data in their possession or control.iv. Upon our request, you must provide a list of your Service Providers and Sub-Service Providers including up-to-date contact information for each, the types and volume of Platform Data shared, and proof of written agreements with your Service Providers to demonstrate compliance with this Section.v. We may prohibit your use of any Service Provider or Sub-Service Provider in connection with your use of Platform or Processing of Platform Data if we believe that (1) they have violated these Terms or other applicable terms or policies or (2) they are negatively impacting Platform, otherMeta Products, Platform Data, or people who useMeta Products, and will provide notice to you if we do.  Promptly upon such notice, you must stop using that Service Provider or Sub-Service Provider in connection with your use of Platform or Processing of Platform Data.vi. We may require that your Service Providers or Sub-Service Providers agree to these Terms or other applicable terms or policies in order to accessMeta Products, Platform, or Platform Data."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "ii. You must ensure that any Service Provider and Sub-Service Provider complies with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies as if they were in your place, and you are responsible for their acts and omissions, including their noncompliance."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "iv. Upon our request, you must provide a list of your Service Providers and Sub-Service Providers including up-to-date contact information for each, the types and volume of Platform Data shared, and proof of written agreements with your Service Providers to demonstrate compliance with this Section."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "b. Tech Providersi. If you are a Tech Provider, you must comply with the other provisions of these Terms, as well as the provisions in this section with respect to your use of Platform and Processing of Platform Data as a Tech Provider.  If the terms conflict, the terms that are more restrictive on you or more protective of us apply.ii. You, as a Tech Provider, understand and agree to the following:1. You will only use Platform and Process Platform Data on behalf of and at the direction of your Client on whose behalf you access it to help such Client to use Platform or Process Platform Data in accordance with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies (\u201cClient\u2019s Purpose\u201d), and not for your own purposes or another Client\u2019s or entity\u2019s purposes (for example, you will not Process Platform Data to build or augment user profiles for your own purposes or another Client\u2019s purposes);2. You will ensure that Platform Data you maintain on behalf of one Client is maintained separately from that of other Clients;3. You will maintain an up-to-date list of your Clients and their contact information and provide it to us if we ask for it;4. You will only share Platform Data in compliance with these Terms (including Sections 3a (\u201cProhibited Practices\u201d), 3b (\u201cAdditional Terms for Restricted Platform Data\u201d), and 5a (\u201cService Providers\u201d)), applicable law and regulations, and all other applicable terms and policies, and only in the following circumstances:a. with your applicable Client, so long as you first contractually prohibit such Client from Processing Platform Data in a way that would violate these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies;b. to the extent required under applicable law or regulation (you must retain proof of the applicable legal or regulatory requirement or request and provide it to us if we ask for it);c. with your Service Provider solely to the extent necessary for your applicable Client\u2019s Purpose; ord. with your Client\u2019s service provider solely to the extent necessary for such Client\u2019s Purpose and when such Client expressly directs you to share the data with such service provider (you must retain proof of the Client\u2019s express direction and provide it to us if we ask for it);5. We may require that your Clients agree to these Terms or other applicable terms or policies in order to accessMeta Products, Platform, or Platform Data through your App.6. You will promptly terminate a Client\u2019s use of ourMeta Products, Platform, or Platform Data through your App if we request it because we believe that the Client (a) has violated these Terms or other applicable terms or policies or (b) is negatively impacting Platform, otherMeta Products, Platform Data, or people who useMeta Products."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "ii. You, as a Tech Provider, understand and agree to the following:1. You will only use Platform and Process Platform Data on behalf of and at the direction of your Client on whose behalf you access it to help such Client to use Platform or Process Platform Data in accordance with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies (\u201cClient\u2019s Purpose\u201d), and not for your own purposes or another Client\u2019s or entity\u2019s purposes (for example, you will not Process Platform Data to build or augment user profiles for your own purposes or another Client\u2019s purposes);2. You will ensure that Platform Data you maintain on behalf of one Client is maintained separately from that of other Clients;3. You will maintain an up-to-date list of your Clients and their contact information and provide it to us if we ask for it;4. You will only share Platform Data in compliance with these Terms (including Sections 3a (\u201cProhibited Practices\u201d), 3b (\u201cAdditional Terms for Restricted Platform Data\u201d), and 5a (\u201cService Providers\u201d)), applicable law and regulations, and all other applicable terms and policies, and only in the following circumstances:a. with your applicable Client, so long as you first contractually prohibit such Client from Processing Platform Data in a way that would violate these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies;b. to the extent required under applicable law or regulation (you must retain proof of the applicable legal or regulatory requirement or request and provide it to us if we ask for it);c. with your Service Provider solely to the extent necessary for your applicable Client\u2019s Purpose; ord. with your Client\u2019s service provider solely to the extent necessary for such Client\u2019s Purpose and when such Client expressly directs you to share the data with such service provider (you must retain proof of the Client\u2019s express direction and provide it to us if we ask for it);5. We may require that your Clients agree to these Terms or other applicable terms or policies in order to accessMeta Products, Platform, or Platform Data through your App.6. You will promptly terminate a Client\u2019s use of ourMeta Products, Platform, or Platform Data through your App if we request it because we believe that the Client (a) has violated these Terms or other applicable terms or policies or (b) is negatively impacting Platform, otherMeta Products, Platform Data, or people who useMeta Products."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "3. You will maintain an up-to-date list of your Clients and their contact information and provide it to us if we ask for it;"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "a. Data Security Requirementsi. You must always have in effect and maintain administrative, physical, and technical safeguards that do the following:1. Meet or exceed industry standards given the sensitivity of the Platform Data;2. Comply with applicable law and regulations, including data security and privacy laws, rules, and regulations; and3. Are designed to prevent any unauthorized (including in violation of these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies) Processing (including, for the avoidance of doubt, access, destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, distribution, or compromise) of Platform Data.ii. You must have a publicly available way for people to report security vulnerabilities in your App to you, and you must promptly address identified deficiencies.iii. You must not solicit, collect, store, cache, proxy, or use Facebook or Instagram login credentials of other Users.iv. You must not transfer or share user IDs or your access token and secret key, except with a Service Provider who helps you build, run, or operate your App."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "ii. You must have a publicly available way for people to report security vulnerabilities in your App to you, and you must promptly address identified deficiencies."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "c. Auditing Rightsi. We or Third-Party Auditors may conduct an Audit, no more than once a calendar year unless there is a Necessary Condition, to ensure that your and your App\u2019s Processing of Platform Data is and has been in compliance with these Terms and all other applicable terms and policies.ii. Audits will be conducted during normal business hours after providing you with at least 10 business days\u2019 written notice (email will suffice), unless we determine in our sole discretion a Necessary Condition requires more immediate access.iii. You will cooperate with the Audits, including by (1) providing all necessary physical and remote access to your IT Systems and Records, and (2) providing information and assistance as reasonably requested (including making your personnel who are knowledgeable about your or your App\u2019s Processing of Platform Data available for our questioning).iv. You will also use commercially reasonable efforts to get permission and cooperation from your Service Providers for us to conduct such Audits with respect to their IT Systems, Records, and applicable personnel.v. You will remedy any non-compliance revealed by an Audit as soon as reasonably practicable (as we determine based on the facts and circumstances), after which we may conduct follow-up Audits to ensure proper remediation of the non-compliance.vi. If an Audit reveals any non-compliance by you or your Service Provider(s) then you will reimburse us for all of our reasonable costs and expenses associated with conducting the Audit and any related follow-up Audits.vii. After these Terms have ended, our Audit rights under this Section will survive until 1 year after the later of when you affirmatively demonstrate that you have stopped Processing all Platform Data and all embodiments thereof that are in your and your Service Providers\u2019 possession or control have been deleted. For the avoidance of doubt, nothing in this Section limits any other rights or remedies we may have by law, in equity, or under these Terms or other applicable terms or policies."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "iv. You will also use commercially reasonable efforts to get permission and cooperation from your Service Providers for us to conduct such Audits with respect to their IT Systems, Records, and applicable personnel."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "e. Suspension and Terminationi. We may take enforcement action against you and your App if we believe, in our sole discretion, that:1. You have not timely responded to our requests related to monitoring or auditing;2. You or your App has violated or may have violated these Terms or any other applicable terms or policies or is negatively impacting Platform, otherMeta Products, Platform Data, or people who useMeta Products;3. It is needed to comply with applicable laws or regulations or otherwise required or requested by a court order or governmental authority; or4. It is needed to protect theMeta Companiesfrom legal or regulatory liability.ii. We may take enforcement action at any time, including while we investigate your App, with or without notice to you. Enforcement can be both automated and manual.  It can include suspending or removing your App, removing your access and your App\u2019s access to Platform, requiring that you stop Processing and delete Platform Data, terminating our agreements with you, or any other action that we consider to be appropriate, including terminating other agreements with you or your ability to useMeta Products.iii. We may suspend or end your App\u2019s access to any Platform APIs, permissions, or features that your App has not used or accessed within a 28-day period with or without notice to you."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "iii. We may suspend or end your App\u2019s access to any Platform APIs, permissions, or features that your App has not used or accessed within a 28-day period with or without notice to you."}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "After you agree to these Terms, any written notice, request, or communications from us to you may be provided via email or mail (for example, to the email address or mailing address in your App account with us) or via notifications within theMeta Products(for example, in your account with us).  You will keep your contact information current, including name, business name, and email."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "This section shall apply to the extent that your Processing of Platform Data includes personal data controlled by Meta Platforms Ireland Limited (\u201cMeta Ireland Data\u201d) and the transfer of such Meta Ireland Data to a territory outside of the European Economic Area that, at the time of such transfer, does not have a positive adequacy decision from the European Commission under Article 45 of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (each an \u201cEEA Data Transfer\u201d)."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "a. For the purposes of Annex I(A) to the Clauses, Meta Platforms Ireland Limited is the \"data exporter\" and you are the \"data importer\" as defined in the Clauses.b. For the purposes of Annex I(B) to the Clauses:i. \u201cCategories of data subjects\u201d are the Users who visit, access, use, or otherwise interact with the App and the products and services of Meta Platforms Ireland Limited;ii. \"Categories of personal data\" are Meta Ireland Data, which includes profile information, photos and videos, location information, communications between Users, information about use of the App and other products and services, payment information, device information, information about visits to third-party websites or Apps that use a \"like\" or \"comment\" button or other service integration, information from third-party partners or the Meta Companies, or as otherwise set forth in the Data Policy;iii. \"Sensitive data\" is personal data about a person's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or data concerning a natural person's sex life or sexual orientation, criminal convictions or alleged commission of an offence;iv. \"Frequency of the transfer\" is on a continuous basis to the extent required to fulfill the purpose outlined in Section 10(b)(v) below;v. Nature and purpose of the data transfer(s)\" is the provision of the App and other products and services by you to Users pursuant to the applicable terms and conditions and Privacy Policy of you and/or your Client; andvi. \"Period for which personal data will be retained\" is as set out in Section 3(d)(i)(2) unless applicable laws require the Meta Ireland Data be retained for a longer period, in which case you shall only retain such Meta Ireland Data for the period required by such applicable laws and subject always to Section 10(d)."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "ii. \"Categories of personal data\" are Meta Ireland Data, which includes profile information, photos and videos, location information, communications between Users, information about use of the App and other products and services, payment information, device information, information about visits to third-party websites or Apps that use a \"like\" or \"comment\" button or other service integration, information from third-party partners or the Meta Companies, or as otherwise set forth in the Data Policy;"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "iii. \"Sensitive data\" is personal data about a person's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade-union membership, genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or data concerning a natural person's sex life or sexual orientation, criminal convictions or alleged commission of an offence;"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "c. For the purposes of Annex I(C) to the Clauses, the competent supervisory authority will be the Data Protection Commission in Ireland; andd. For the purposes of Annex II to the Clauses, you will implement and maintainMeta's Technical and Organisational Measures."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "a. In Table 1 of the Approved Addendum, the parties' details are as follows:i. Meta Platforms, Inc. is the \"data exporter\" and you are the \"data importer\" as defined in the Approved Addendum.ii. The parties details and key contact information are:Meta Platforms, Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94205, USA, and the contact person's details are as notified by the data exporter to the data importer from time to time.Developer's details and key contact information are your details notified to Meta Platforms, Inc. from time to time.iii. The parties agree that execution of these Terms by the parties shall constitute execution of the Approved Addendum."}, {"question": "How can I contact Pomona College?", "answer": "ii. The parties details and key contact information are:Meta Platforms, Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA 94205, USA, and the contact person's details are as notified by the data exporter to the data importer from time to time.Developer's details and key contact information are your details notified to Meta Platforms, Inc. from time to time."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "b. \"Approved Addendum\" means the International Data Transfer Addendum to the Approved EU SCCs, Version B1.0, issued by the Information Commissioner under s119A of the Data Protection Act 2018 and dated 21 March 2022, as may be amended, replaced or superseded by the Information Commissioner."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "d. \u201cClauses\u201d means the standard contractual clauses annexed to European Commission Decision (EU) 2021/914."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "l. \u201cProcess\u201d means any operation or set of operations performed on data or sets of data, whether or not by automated means, including use, collection, storage, sharing, or transmission."}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "o. \u201cRestricted Platform Data\u201d means Platform Data that (i) reasonably can be used to identify a particular User or device; (ii) is accessed using the permissions listedhere; or (iii) we otherwise designate as Restricted. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Restricted Platform Data does not include data that can be accessed using the permissions listedhere."}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Enable any platform level controls where available"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Have a system in place for logging access to user data, tracing where user data was sent and stored"}, {"question": "Where is Pomona College located?", "answer": "Monitor transfers of user data and key points where user data can leave the system (e.g., third parties, public endpoints)"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Be familiar with basic app security practices includingAssessing permissions and data needs (aligning data access to purpose of use)Testing APIs and endpoints for data leakageTesting transmissions to and from third parties for data leakageScanning app and code for common security flaws before deployment"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Assessing permissions and data needs (aligning data access to purpose of use)"}, {"question": "What is the mission of Pomona College?", "answer": "Testing transmissions to and from third parties for data leakage"}, {"question": "What is the address of Pomona College?", "answer": "Be familiar with basic coding practices to address fundamental security concerns"}]